Hello. How are you doing? What's up, people? Hey, Mantis! Might not stay for the stream, but not too interested in Terraria.
But I would like to say I've been enjoying the heck out of your content. The Breath of the Wild and Subnautica playthrough so far.
Dude, I'm so happy you're enjoying those. I had a ton of fun with those. Thanks for stopping by, Mantis and saying hi. I appreciate it.
Have fun. Doing pretty well, if I say so myself. Nice one, oopsie. That's always nice to hear.
Eh, I'll watch half an hour. Nice. I'll take it. Beatbox day? I don't know. Actually, I'm kind of tired today.
So, I think today is gonna be a chill stream. I'm gonna stop and smell the flowers a bit more.
Because I've been fucking jumping everywhere, shooting things, slapping things, getting slapped myself as well on occasion, but...
You know? How's your day, man? It's been kind of busy today, but I'm finally sitting down and I'm going to relax now.
I'm looking forward to that. 24-hour stream today! Yan! How dare you?
Maybe I'll do it one day. Maybe not 24 hours is kind of insane. I could maybe see myself doing a 12-hour stream at some point in the future.
Although, that is also kind of nuts.
So, yeah, I'm gonna be doing some more building today. Looking at the... what should I call it?
There's this book in the game that tells you things about enemies and characters and all that.
I'll be looking at that. I'm gonna do some fishing. And, yeah, you know? Being a little creative. Amazing.
Oh, yeah! Okay, guys. Yes, the bestiary. That's it. That's the word I was looking for. Thank you.
256-hour stream is fine. What a specific amount of hours. I like it.
Hey, from Australia. What's up, couch enthusiast? I love your name.
And I can't tell what your profile picture is, but to me, it looks like a hamster that is chilling. On a couch, maybe?
Then again, I'm far away from the screen. The chat is small. It's kind of hard to see. That's what I imagine now.
You are now a hamster. Okay. I'm just gonna go in right in, guys. I'm gonna quickly close the chat.
I'm sorry for just abruptly just closing you down. I'm sorry if I don't get to answer all your questions,
but there's just so many people and I wanna... as egotistical as it sounds, I just wanna play my game.
So, I'm gonna get a jump right in, basically.
Oh, man.
Guys, I have a confession to make.
I don't think I like this railway.
I don't. It's ugly. It makes me unhappy. When I look at it, I'm disgusted.
I'm unhappy with myself and what I've done.
And one day, I will remove it. Maybe that day is today. Who knows?
But would you look at this place right here? It's crowded. There's many people.
People I don't even remember that I let inside, but they're here anyway. Like, who the fuck is Haley?
And I guess Edmond also... Who's Ella, even? I have no clue. They're just here.
So today, I'm gonna do a meet and greet. And perhaps even relocate some of these.
Rosalva is not supposed to be here, and she's definitely not supposed to be playing...
Stone Rock Scissor. With this guy. Wait a minute. It's stone... stone... stone... paper scissor.
Is that how you say that? Stone... paper scissor? Something like that.
Izzy, you motherfucker. What's up, Edmond? What are you doing up there? Are you trapped? Hold on. No, you're not.
To where I younger, I would ask Kathleen out. I used to be quite the lady killer.
You know, this guy is the creepy guy, isn't he? This is the guy that said all these nasty things at some point, and he's still doing it.
What makes you happy, Edmond?
The local population is like living with dead weight on my back. I hate Ella the mechanic, and I don't know why.
Brother, me too. On that we can agree. I don't know who she is, but I hate her already. I'm kidding. I actually don't know her.
You know what this house needs? More blinking lights. Maybe we should be doing that.
Some... I need to really organize everything here. This is a mess. This has become something... it's like a hotel at this point.
The Overlook Hotel, almost. What makes you happy?
I'm gonna need a way bigger power source for this many people. I hate it.
Fjell the Godland Tingerer makes my heart flutter. I need to get that checked.
I don't really like that Dante the Arms Dealer won't leave me alone.
I hate how Edmond the Clothier doesn't know how to treat a woman.
Yeah, I would say Edmond the Clothier doesn't know how to treat anyone.
What do you sell?
Right, all this stuff. Wait a minute, plus 20 range.
Is this range universal?
You know what? We're gonna do some testing.
Yoink! Thank you for the red wrench.
Oh, wait a minute. This also gives plus 20 range.
This has to be ranged when placing objects, I imagine.
It's gotta be, right?
It's a, wait, it's a material.
Wait a minute.
Uh, what was your name again?
Bradley?
Or whoever the fuck you are.
I need to know about this right here.
A multicolor wrench.
I don't like that. I like my wrench red.
Am I, am I crazy?
I like the red wrench.
Oh, right click while holding to edit wire settings. So it actually does...
It does things.
It does all the things that these things do.
But in one, it's a multi-tool.
Multi-tool.
Yeah.
Okay, so, you know what? Hold on.
One sec.
We need to write down what people want and who they don't like.
Because fuck if I remember that shit.
There's way too much.
Let's see here.
So Ella...
does not like...
um...
the creep, Edmond.
Uh, although they're playing the stone paper scissor now.
Hello.
Ella?
Hey Oliver, did you just come from Fjell's?
Did he say anything about me by chance? Right, you liked Fjell.
Plus on Fjell.
Okay, good.
Way bigger power source.
Okay, so you want less people.
Got it.
Less people for you.
Good.
Alright, you're down.
Edmond.
Of course embroidery is hard.
If it wasn't hard, no one would do it.
That's what makes it great.
Local population is like living with...
Yeah, so what does that mean?
With dead weight on my back?
Does that mean he's also not into living with too many people?
I hate Ella the mechanic and I don't know why.
Yeah, okay.
So Edmond, even though you're kind of weird...
Uh, you do not want Ella.
Gotcha, on that one.
And I guess she also doesn't want him.
So, match made in heaven right there.
Now...
I made a house here.
Tell me what's wrong with that house.
Excuse me.
Rosalva, why are you here?
Why are you actually here?
Hold on.
I'm gonna go west.
And while I go west...
I'm gonna remove.
This is gonna be horrible, isn't it?
I already regret my decisions right now.
Maybe this is not the most optimal thing.
There's gotta be a better way of removing that, I imagine.
For now, I'm gonna go west to Rosalva's actual home.
She needs to be relocated.
I made such a pretty little place for her.
And she spat all over it by coming back to the commune.
Like, look at this place right here.
How is this not glorious?
In every single way.
Okay, maybe they're zombies and stuff.
But it's about the interior here.
Location doesn't matter too much.
She likes the wood, right?
God, this weapon is fantastic.
Definitely my favorite weapon in the game right now.
Get away.
Why is that blinking?
Rosalva.
Blop!
Now stay!
Can I lock it or something?
Can I somehow lock that?
Okay, it's still there.
She should be coming here soon then.
Look at that nice damage there.
Let's also close the doors behind us.
Maybe she doesn't like the zombies, actually.
Which is understandable.
I understand.
But that's how it's gonna be.
Now, I wanna check, first of all, if any of these residents here have a preference for a biome.
Because in that case, I'm just gonna instantly teleport them over there.
I'm gonna say teleport, I mean, I manually go over there and I make a home for them.
Let's see here.
Hano?
When I'm not doing business, I'd much rather be alone.
Okay.
I hate feeling crammed in.
Oh no, the forest does not inspire me. Don't like, don't like.
Dante, the arm steel has good eyes for vividness in business. I like it, yes?
Okay, so, Hano.
You like, Dante.
And you wanna be alone.
No forest.
I gotcha, man.
I feel like the desert would be appropriate for you.
I don't know what gives me that impression, but...
You are going to the desert, Hano.
And you're going right now.
That's it, you're being relocated.
Let's see what I have.
I'm going to make you a house of mud.
Maybe not.
Can I actually make a...
I want to make a desert...
a sand home for him.
I want to make a...
biome appropriate home.
Let's also deposit all that.
Silt.
Ah, these two. Oh, yeah, right.
I discovered that liquid, remember?
The magic lake on the ground.
Oh, and I got an ethereum block.
I kind of forgot about this, hold on.
I got to talk to Bradley about this.
Bradley?
I'm just going to call you Brad, if that's okay.
Ethereum brick.
And wall. Okay, so it's like...
Hey, that's it?
It's just construction stuff.
Oh, man, I was expecting this to be...
something I could make weapons out of.
But I guess it makes sense that I can't, because it's kind of...
blocky looking, it's not really an ore.
Per se.
Hmm.
That's fine.
What else do I have?
What would be a sand block?
You know what, let's take some sand with us.
Yeah.
Let's take a workbench as well.
So the question I have right now...
In order to craft the...
living wood things, I needed the living loom, right?
This one.
Here I can make stuff...
that is like the stuff that is in Rosalva's house right now.
How do I always make sure that I can craft, let's say, sand-themed items?
Right?
So I need to figure that out.
Let's take some wood first of all.
And some wool. Let's take the basics here.
And some glass.
Didn't I also make a window...
at some point?
Bradley?
Tell me about the wood again.
Let's see here.
So this is living wood.
I guess not everything has to be wood related though.
Like there are things made of stone too.
Right, so...
Oh, you know what, I should probably give him sand, honestly.
If we're talking sand...
Oh, wait, sandstone...
What is this?
Oh, it requires silt.
Nah, I don't have silt, I used it all.
Balling sand.
See, these runs right here could be appropriate.
I need to see what the items are called, the standard items.
Where's the stone? So this is a stone block, right?
This is just wood, this is what I used to make these walls and the roof in this place.
Let's bring stone as well.
Stone seems good.
And snow, maybe I'll make it like a little igloo or something in the snow region.
Maybe one of these will want to be there.
Oh, maybe ice is the appropriate one for that actually.
Not snow.
Marble!
Maybe that's nice.
Let's take some more wall as well.
Hardened, hold on, hardened sand block.
What can I make with this?
Magic, what the fuck is that?
I need a crystal ball.
Crystal, can probably be made from crystal.
I don't have crystal right now.
I have a diamond, but that's not crystal.
Sand wall, there it is.
But this is hardened sand wall.
Uh...
If I make sandstone slabs, or sandstone bricks even...
So what's the difference?
Nothing. You can make one of each.
Heavy workbench and furnace.
Let's do the furnace one. That seems like more stable building material, doesn't it?
I can make a great brick?
Thank you.
Let's see how that looks.
Sandstone brick there.
There are bricks. Makes sense, I guess.
What about the hardened sand block?
What does that look like?
Okay, that's like loose sand.
Well, hardened loose sand. This is not like a construction thing.
Whereas the bricks are obviously construction.
Okay, but there was another one I could make.
Which one was it?
So this one I tried.
Wasn't there another one I could make?
Sandstone slab.
Heavy workbench. That's that one.
Is it not?
Wait, is this the heavy workbench?
No, oh, this is the sawmill.
Never mind. Wait a minute.
This is the heavy workbench.
Let's try the slab.
Let's see what this one does.
Then we have this one.
Huh, it look kind of similar.
I think I like the slabs the most.
But I guess you can vary it.
Maybe this is all super unnecessary, but it's fun.
Okay, I will actually make the rest of these slabs, I think.
Yeah, I have decided.
Let's slab it up.
Plop.
Now we have all kinds of things to choose between here.
Platforms we also have.
Which is nice.
An arcane depth meter.
I want to put this in here.
Up here.
And these two...
I guess we can put them in a miscellaneous for now.
So let me chest something right here.
So...
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, you there!
The hell are you doing in my house?
So if I don't have this right now...
Wait, does it...
Okay, goes to there.
Oh.
Yeah, I don't know, I don't know.
Last 20 range.
I thought maybe it would allow me to...
Build things from further away, which would be kind of useful.
Sometimes I have to jump up on another platform just to build higher and stuff.
I see more.
Sword beats paper.
Let's see, what do you got?
You know what, I'll take another iron animal.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Dante, do you have anything new?
No, you still... Oh my god, look how shit this is now.
Compared to the weapons I have now, my goodness.
I was drooling over that weapon some time in the past.
But now, I don't even want it.
Okay, more tall.
You don't like many people. Okay, let's see here.
More tall.
Hate people.
Let's see, what else?
You love Driskan.
And Ella.
Okay.
Those two?
I want to strap Fjell the goblin tingerer to a rocket and watch what happens.
I want to strap Dante the arms dealer to a rocket.
Okay, so you hate those two, huh? You hate weapons.
Okay, Dante and Fjell.
No wait, Fjell is the...
He's more of a tingerer.
Got it.
Uh...
I can't decide what I like more.
Parties or after parties?
What about the pre-party?
Huh?
Did you just fucking spray things at me?
I have a job for you.
I don't think you can say no either. Not right now, Izzy.
I said no.
Stay mad.
Fjell, I just finished my newest creation.
This version doesn't explode violently if you breathe on it too hard.
That's a good change.
Whatever you did, keep it up.
Oh! That's it!
That's what I need.
Thank you.
Lovely.
Beautiful stuff.
Dude, let's have a builder outfit.
A builder...
uh...
loadout.
Yeah, let's do that.
What would be super nice on that?
Or maybe this is already the best outfit I have for building right now.
At least for now.
Let me put that in there.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Lovely.
I collected critters like you once, then I took a cursed fox bite to the knee.
This joke just never goes away, does it?
I get a little anxious around a lot of people.
I, like, don't want that.
I love animals, so naturally the forest is, like, the best place ever.
Yes!
Alright.
So you want to be in a little cabin by yourself with a lot of animals.
You're a crazy cat lady.
Gotcha.
You know what? We can make that happen right now.
We are in the forest, m'lady.
I shall construct for you a forest hut.
Let's see here.
Maybe it'll be made of stone.
What do you think of that?
We require a little bit of a flat area here.
Dude, I could make, like, a little hobbit place in the earth.
I kind of like the idea of having a basement.
Dude. Basement.
Oh yeah, I'm definitely basementing.
Not right now, though. But for the main house.
Okay. Let's see.
You know what? We gotta use wood here.
Just do something like this.
Oh, whoa. Hello. Excuse me.
Get out of here.
I wonder if this is far enough from the settlement.
Okay. And now?
Okay, it's smart enough to know that I don't want to go deeper than this.
That's nice.
What does marble look like?
Oh no!
Fill it up again.
Um, I need wood.
Top, top, top, top, top, top, top, top.
Nice flooring here.
Let me actually put it there as well.
Oh wait, I have to remember, I don't need to remove the dirt first.
I can just sort of place it.
Dammit.
I will remove this, though.
It's making me a little unhappy.
Oh wait a minute, I should make...
It was possible to make a shovel, wasn't it?
I remember something about a shovel.
There we go.
Oh, I forgot the doors.
Crap cake.
That's okay, we have this.
Uh, wooden door.
A wooden door is fine for now.
Let's make two.
One on each side.
I wish I could just place it like that.
Get away.
Also you.
I am constructing.
Can't you see?
I don't like the little thing there.
So we're gonna make a platform.
This is so finicky.
How do I...
Wait, where did it just go?
Slide?
Oh, there it is.
Oh no, not like that.
God, I don't understand how this works.
I did it before, didn't I?
Hold on.
I did it over here, I believe.
Let's see what I did.
Ah, it's a bigger drop-off.
Maybe I can't.
Also, let me remove this. I don't like the way this looks.
Okay. Anyway, we need a wall.
Let's make a nice wall here.
A wood wall.
Ah, let me take a sip of my coffee.
Look at my little turtle hanging out on the roof.
Isn't that cute?
Let's put an animal...
Nah, yeah. Why not?
This can be a little...
I don't even know.
Okay, so she wanted animals, right?
I wonder if there's a way to place an animal here.
Like, anchor it to this place.
But I guess there's a bunch of slimes.
Maybe they count, you know?
Maybe she'll love the slimes.
Now, the window.
A glass wall.
We have a little window there.
And let's say...
Something like that.
Doesn't that look cool?
Hold on.
Maybe two windows is fine, and then we have some furniture over here.
I think that would look badass.
Um...
Let me see what I have in my construction box.
I have all kinds of things there.
I absolutely love how the turtle has a little helicopter blade.
So, in my box of goodies, what do I have?
I wonder what she would... Let me see her.
So, she's...
I don't even know, man.
What would you like?
A bookcase, maybe.
Maybe you'd like to read.
And...
Great wave.
Maybe.
Let's just bring some stuff.
The Cursed Man.
Hand to Earth.
Skelehead? I don't know about that.
These are all very demonic.
There's so much demon going on here.
What's in here? More.
Do I have anything in here that's nice?
Mudblock extractinator.
Let's bring that with us.
That's fine for now.
Man, I kind of want to make the roof look a little more...
roofy.
You know what I mean?
I have an idea. Hold on a second.
Let's try something here.
What if I...
Something like that.
Just vary it a little bit, you know?
Not bad.
That actually did so much.
I like it.
That's amazing.
See, I can't reach right now.
Even with my tool belt.
But I can do this.
The hook is actually fantastic.
There we go.
Wall time, baby!
Ah, we got up.
This works.
There we go. Oh, look at that! That's already so much better.
Huh?
I like that. I like that a lot.
Way more character to this building now.
Okay.
We can make the window just a bit bigger now.
Look at that!
So nice.
Let's have a nice painting here.
Like that.
And we obviously need a bookcase.
Well, maybe not in front of the window. That would be kind of stupid.
We can't move that again.
You can sit here and read. How about that?
I need to make a table?
I guess this could be a table.
That works. Uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
We've got incoming.
I'm building, though.
Alright. Can they even get in?
Okay.
They can get in.
Sometimes they can't. It's a bit...
Oh my god, I'm an idiot.
I thought I had my weapon equipped. I didn't.
God damn it, guys. I'm building.
I'm building right now. Can't you see?
Just leave me alone while I make this house, please.
It actually looks kind of neat in here.
You know, with all the lights and stuff.
Very nice.
Okay, construction. Do we have any specialized lights?
We have a dungeon stuff.
We can take that, I guess.
What is this? Alchemy table.
And another bewitching table.
Yeah, I don't really have that many great things.
Haley, I shall protect you.
God, this is actually annoying. I want to build right now.
I don't want to fight.
Today, I'm a passive man.
What did you just say?
Ahh! Thank you, me wrath!
Okay.
It doesn't say... there's no bar or anything saying how long this will last.
You know what?
Is that... what's happening here?
They can never get in on that side.
Hold on.
Please fuck off.
What is the difference? Why does this look different than that?
It looks different.
Why does it look different?
Can you come in?
What?!
Okay, I don't... why can they not come in on this side?
They've never been able to, now that I think about it.
Look, they can't get in.
What the fuck?
Wait, is it because of the torch, maybe?
There's a torch right next to the door.
Maybe the torch is blocking them.
I need to go kill them, though.
Also, I can't believe...
Apparently, I lost a lot of money.
Because I just can't find it.
And I had a platinum.
Like, this weapon right here is the tits.
My goodness.
Okay, is it working?
Hey! Zombie, come back!
It's the blood moon, don't you know?
Let's see it.
The torch!
The torch did the trick?
Unbelievable.
Well, what a weird little gimmick.
I mean, I'll take it.
Definitely.
Okay.
Who the fuck are you?
The groom?
Oh, you're an enemy!
I thought you came to hang out.
Till death.
Kill the groom.
Okay. I killed the groom.
What did I get?
Did I get anything?
I don't think I got anything.
Wait a minute!
Is this doing AOE?
This just killed all three at once!
This is even better than I thought!
Wait a minute.
Is this actually AOE?
I mean, it does sort of explode in the sparkles.
Dude, this thing is...
Wow. Unbelievably good.
Alright.
Why are these purple?
Is it because of the blood moon?
Look at that. They can't get in now.
I have now monster-proofed the building.
Let's see if he can get in here. There's no drop here.
He can't!
This is amazing.
So now I want to summon.
Flop!
Go kill them!
No! Go outside!
Okay, it's not going to actually kill them while I hide in here.
That's too bad.
Alright. Fair enough, I guess.
That would be a little...
...exploity, wouldn't it?
Is there anything else I need in here?
I have lights, I have a bookcase, I have this.
Now let me relocate.
Let's see here.
Wait, where are you?
Catlin?
Rosalva?
Huh?
Oh, over here.
There you go.
The zoologist. Go study animals.
I want to plant trees around this, by the way.
Let's make a nice forest around here.
I wonder if I can plant trees on top of the house.
If I make a layer of dirt, and I put saplings in there.
I'm going to test it.
Whoa! I just...
Oh, look at this!
You can totally cheese them.
The AOE.
Not that I need to cheese them because they're so easy, but you know, it's possible.
Unbelievable.
You're not a damn blot moon.
Well, I'm getting a bunch of money.
Wait, 56 silver, that's actually a lot.
Just for killing someone randomly like that.
There she is.
Okay.
Open space, happy in the forest.
Good. Run.
Play.
Hunt.
Bro, you are fucking weird.
I mean, that's fine and all.
I'm just saying.
You're going to be weird.
But it's kind of creeping me out a little bit, not going to lie.
It's making me want to run away.
How about you fight with me, Haley?
Help me fight off the horde here.
I need your help.
Okay, I need to remember what I... Oh, here we go.
Close that door.
I got to remember which item it was that made me plant trees.
I think I have it in my organic's box.
550th zombie, what an oddly specific number.
What do I have?
Oh, wait!
Dude, I'm bringing her bunnies.
That's what I have to do.
Dude, squirrels, bunnies, fucking penguins, owls.
She'll get all the animals.
Acorn.
That's what I need.
Yeah, this weapon is incredible.
I got... Bro, can I just please fucking...
make this house?
Wait a minute.
Oops.
These things didn't grow.
Maybe I need to have them separated.
It just now occurred to me that these never grew.
Maybe this is too close. Yeah, okay.
It must be too close.
Let's see here.
Fuck, where did I just put there?
Let's say I used the...
Like, there?
I don't know, maybe, maybe...
Okay, so here, hold on.
Actually, here they're quite close to each other.
So this is one, two, three, four, five.
Maybe five is the...
Hey, hey!
Will you stop that?
God dang it.
I guess we're fighting this.
Game won't leave me alone here for a second.
I guess I can go in here.
They're not going to get to me.
Ah, that's not true, though.
The sorcerer is going to get to me.
But I'm going to let these guys stack up here on the door and then...
Oh, they broke the door!
Never mind.
Holy shit.
All right, then, fair play.
Let me put this here for now.
Ailey, come back inside.
Is it me, or is this the goblin army becoming more dangerous?
As time goes on.
Maybe every new goblin army is more dangerous than the last.
Probably something like that, right?
I mean, it's money, and I need money.
I lost all my money somehow.
How much do I even have?
I don't even have that much right now.
Okay, at least I can see the bar in the bottom left.
Do I know how long it takes?
Oh, my God. Everything's on fire.
Ailey, where are you?
Go inside.
Go inside, Ailey.
Something, dude.
I mean, the saver is still the best one for these types of engagement here.
The no mana cost is incredible.
But these guys have a lot of HP.
She's losing HP.
This is bad.
I've got to take care of the sorcerers there.
She's actually dying.
Bro, go inside!
You hear me?
I shall protect you.
Okay, this is amazing for... yeah.
This weapon right here is... this is it.
Yep.
Oh, there you are.
We did it.
We are victorious.
Now get inside, Ailey.
Dumbass.
Wait, are you bugging out because of this thing?
Delete this.
I don't want him.
A great wave. No, it's too big.
Blood moon rising right there.
And then we need a torch there.
That looks like a good home.
Now go inside, Ailey.
Wow, like, I've never seen a full moon.
For some reason, it's like I pass out every time one's around.
Oh, is that what happened?
You passed out?
Sakura sapling.
Wait, yo.
Wait, you sell a whip...
and black studded saddle.
Wait a minute, what is this?
We'll dig through blocks and lay new track if carrying minecart tracks?
Dude!
That's kind of crazy.
Whoa, hold on.
Wait, oh my God, it's a tree.
A Sakura tree?
No way.
Yellow willow.
Let's try that.
There.
This one is not growing yet, but...
Let's see if it will grow or not.
Maybe it's too close. This one is definitely...
Well, then again, I built the house after the tree grew, right, so...
Kind of hard to know, I guess.
Let's just wait and see what happens.
Now, Ailey.
Did I bring you bunnies?
I'm not sure I did.
You don't want the dungeon stuff, do you?
Probably not.
Okay, this is a good house for you.
Maybe I'll even do one more row here.
Look at that. Ah, that looks good, that looks good.
And then we got to remove this because it's not that good.
Let's put that torch there instead.
Or there.
There we go.
And you're safe now.
I'll be back later to check on these saplings to see how things are progressing.
Speaking of saplings, by the way.
Let me try this one over here.
Just to see, just want to see.
And then, okay, so obviously these are not going to grow because they are here and nothing's happened.
Maybe it needs even ground as well.
Probably that's what that is.
Let me try something here.
So this one is too close.
Let's do five separation.
So one, two, three, four.
Five.
Three, four, five.
Here we can test whether or not this will grow because it's like a little slanted on the side.
How is it actually slanted? Hold on.
How is it slanted?
Wait a minute.
Dirt.
Can I do that too?
Oh, wait! No, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Oh, it's slanting!
Oh, wait a minute.
It's rotating.
Hold on, can I...
Oh, no, wait, that removes the wall. I was trying to see if I could rotate the chair.
Hold on.
No, that removes the door.
God damn it.
Oh, this is so weird.
That's not what I want.
Bring back the wood.
There.
Door.
So, hold on.
Oh!
I don't know why I just got so excited.
I feel like that's a big thing.
Oh, my God.
Look at that.
Ta-da!
And then we can fill the wall because it's not full yet.
Oh, no, it's kind of... Oh, wait. Oh, hammer?
So, okay, hold on.
Oh, no, it's going to have, like, little cracks in the wall then.
That's okay, I guess.
Can't win them all.
All right.
That's it for now.
I have ideas now.
Next stop, by the way, we go to desert.
Actually, we're going now.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I had some desert stuff here, didn't I?
Hold on now.
Sandstone Workbench.
I'm bringing that.
Leave this here as well.
And that one.
I guess these as well.
Let's bring some doors and a table.
Now, the question is,
how am I going to craft...
Oh!
Is it that simple?
Is it just with the sandstone bench that I can make sandstone things?
It's not just cosmetic?
Is that what's happening?
Uh, Bradley?
Let's say I wanted to make the sandstone workbench myself.
How would I do it?
Is it really?
Oh, hold on.
Okay, this one doesn't do anything.
Sandstone Brickwall.
Oh, this one doesn't do anything either.
Heart and Sand Block.
I can make Heart and Sand Wall.
No, that's not what I want.
Maybe, is it really just wood?
I mean, I can make all kinds of wooden stuff, naturally.
So, why do I not get something like this when I use the sand?
I guess, hold on, I guess I used all my sand, like an idiot.
I have no more sand, actually.
Sun Plate.
I have this, actually.
What about that?
Sandstone Block.
What's that?
And Lion X?
I don't want to do that.
That sounds bad.
Smooth Sandstone.
Why would I do that?
I'm gonna try it, but...
It's also material.
Okay, Bradley.
What about the Smooth Sandstone?
There it is!
Okay.
So, we need Smooth Sandstone.
Easy peasy.
So, we need Sandstone Blocks.
Gotcha!
What am I doing here?
Put it back.
Let's smooth the shit out of this.
Holy crap!
Maybe a bit overkill.
Let's not use all of it.
And now...
Oh my god.
You know what?
Troff.
Oh!
There's my money!
I thought I lost it all!
But I...
I had more, but I guess I used some last time.
So, maybe I didn't lose it.
I'm just blind, dude!
Hehey!
Fuck yeah, dude!
Fuck yeah!
Hehey!
Put in all this stuff.
Also that and that.
Stone.
That made me feel great.
No, leave this here.
Put this in here.
This one, that one, this one.
And this...
Put it up here.
In you go.
And now...
I think we're ready to craft a bunch of shit.
And I'm taking this one with me.
I just killed something.
But hold on.
Can I craft everything here or do I need to...
Do I need the heavy work bench for that, huh?
Wait a minute.
Do I actually need the heavy?
Let's see here.
So I walk like this.
I walk closer, closer.
Everything pops up.
This has to be the normal work bench just by proximity.
Okay, it's confirmed.
We are going to the desert.
Here.
All men, right by the lake!
Yeah!
Let's make a little fishing hut!
Let's have a couple people there.
Does anyone want to go to the desert actually?
Let me quickly check.
Who's a desert person?
Uh, Hano.
Looks like a desert person.
Who else?
Hold on.
Hano just likes Dante.
Does not like the forest.
I heard there's a doll that looks very similar to Bradley somewhere in the underworld.
I like to...
Okay, let's see here.
So, Dante.
Let me write your name.
Let's see here.
I can't do it with so many people watching, so you hate people.
I get you, man. I get you.
Catlin the Nurse Ever.
Okay, you like Catlin?
Gotcha.
You don't like Lion Pines.
Mine is Lion.
The Golfer.
I'd really like to use Mortal Demolitionist as a ranged target, so you hate him too, huh?
No Mortal.
No Mortal. Mortal.
All right, Dante and Hano.
You shall be sharing a condo in the beautiful land of the... of the sand.
The desert.
You are going to the desert.
I feel like the desert is the perfect place for someone like Dante anyway to test out his arms.
Wait, am I destroying blocks with this?
Did I just make that hole?
I guess not. I'm imagining things.
Okay, where shall the hut be?
On the left side.
So what is this right here? Sand block.
I don't have a lot of that.
I kind of want to get more of that.
So let me get more of that.
Get rid of this cactus.
That's good enough for me.
Dante, can you just leave me alone while I build things, for fuck's sake?
It gets a little... to be a little too much sometimes with all the fucking constant fighting.
Sand, there, there.
Here.
And then...
Take care of this.
See, okay, is this because it's rotated?
Aha!
Look at that. I am finally understanding the hammer.
It rotates. It reorients.
Speaking of the orient, this is where we are right now.
I'm gonna remove this.
Jesus Christ, leave me alone!
Thank you.
Here, the house shall be.
I was about to say, maybe I should mow the lawn, but there's no lawn here.
I can remove all plants, but I don't want to do that.
Now...
Where's my...
Oh wait, did I...
Did I deposit all my stuff like an idiot?
The stuff I need?
Oh no, I have it here.
Take that.
I guess we can use the wood here as well.
Palm wood, actually.
Does that look different?
It totally does!
I thought all wood was equal.
Well, I guess not, because we know living wood is a thing.
But dude, I'm gonna use palm wood.
The palm wood.
Maybe I'll make a... Oh, dude!
I have an idea.
Remember the platforms we saw?
The pillars.
We saw some construction somewhere, I think, underground.
I'm gonna make a house on stilts.
That way, enemies can't get to it!
Bro, this is genius.
House on stilts?
What should the stilts be? Probably wood.
Let's see here.
Something like that.
Let's put it to...
There.
And then...
I need more palm wood.
I guess this also kind of looks nice.
But that's not really what I was looking for here.
Hold on, what am I looking for? I need to think about this.
I wish these enemies would leave me the fuck alone.
It's literally every five seconds an enemy approaches.
Not even half a minute I can get.
It's actually insane.
I mean, it is during the night, but even during the day I feel like they're here.
Because it just became night now, and I had problems before as well.
But I can't really skip the night it seems, so...
I need to think.
Sand block.
What I want to do...
Is something like that.
Oh, actually...
We're gonna have platforms there.
Oh, wait, I can't...
Oh, I know what to do, I know what to do.
I'm gonna make background stilts.
You know what I mean?
I kind of forgot how I did that. I made some in the other house.
Wait a minute. I need to remember what I did there.
I did something smart.
Where is it?
There! Look at that, that's what I want.
How did I...
Wouldn't beam.
Aha!
Let's see here.
It looks like that.
Pomwood wall.
That would be nice.
Oh!
Cactus items!
Yo!
Yes!
Dude!
Oh, but these also look amazing.
God damn.
Anyway, the beam.
Let's see here.
Any beams?
How do I make the beam?
Here.
Oh, I need to be close to the sawmill.
Okay, I see.
Wooden beam.
Sandstone column!
I think that's what I want.
Dude, I want to make all of these, by the way.
A sandstone plaque.
Oh, yeah!
Hell yeah!
Let's make 40 of that.
Get rid of the banner.
We don't want it.
What's with all this?
Let's...
Did I get three shackles right now?
Fuck off!
And a stupid weapon.
Nobody wants that.
I have a top hat?
Where'd I get that?
Wait a minute, what?
Put that on the rack.
Any room left?
There's not.
Oh!
Oh, never mind.
What I have is better.
Pedalers hat.
I mean...
Ah.
Ah!
Oh, wait, it's a vanity thing, right?
Oh, yeah.
This looks so funny.
Okay, here we go.
Check this shit out.
I'm about to use some...
Wait, where is it?
There.
The sandstone column.
Because look at this.
I can walk through it.
House on stilts.
Oh, that was a bit too far to go right there.
There.
Look at that.
And then I want to make...
Put this here.
Please just leave me alone.
I need to make the palm wood platform.
I believe.
There.
It also makes sandstone platform, but no palm wood.
Let's make like 16.
Something like that.
We could have... hmm.
Yeah, I'm trying to think here.
I guess it would be wasted space not to utilize the bottom part here, right?
It would be kind of wasted.
Oh man, I have an idea for a house. I have an idea.
But I need more palm wood.
Can I grow these palm woods?
What if I put an acorn here?
Would that make a...
Wait.
No, that doesn't look right.
Cactus.
Bro, how do I grow these palm trees?
I need more palm wood.
What is... a grape?
Ah, fuck, I need more palm wood.
No, I don't want to remove it. It looks nice.
Do we...
Get away from me.
Oh man, how the fuck do I make that?
Okay, hold on. I need to make a test here.
Do I get anything special from removing a palm tree that I didn't notice before?
Maybe I get an ingredient to plant a new one.
Let's see here.
I get palm wood.
And that's it.
I don't know, man.
Fuck, I can't use palm wood then. Okay, we have to use some other material. I don't have enough of it.
Is the sad truth?
It's very sad.
We have to use sand.
It's sand time.
Smooth?
No, not smooth.
Let's use...
No, not that.
What's the other one I had?
A nice one.
Sandstone brick.
Like, oh.
What's up with the random lines here in the...
Why does it look like that?
Is that me doing something?
Huh, maybe it's random.
All right.
And now I can make platforms.
Sandstone platform.
Let's try that.
Yeah, that looks...
It looks pretty neat.
I like it.
Make it a bit larger.
Larger.
That way I can just jump up like that.
And it'll look nice.
And then...
Good.
What I want to do is this. Check it out.
Oh, wait a minute.
If I hold it in...
Oh, is it based on when I let go?
No, okay, it's not.
So I'll do that.
There.
And then...
I'm gonna do this now.
Hold on.
I have no idea why I'm doing this, but it sounds cool in my mind when it's done.
Something like that.
Just to make it a bit buried here.
Variety is the spice of life, as they say.
Look at that!
We have a little flag up here or some bullshit?
I like it.
And then...
Let's see if we can make that sand wall, huh?
What, sand...
Smooth sandstone wall or sandstone brick wall?
Why not both?
Let's take like a bit of this, see how that looks.
And let's take some smooth sandstone wall.
There we go.
Oh, well, well, well, well.
I think the bottom part here could be nice.
Oh my god, can you just leave me alone what's happening?
Alright, you know what?
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go ham on you guys now.
Very bloodlust!
There's no progress meter or anything.
This is so weird.
Oh wait, I'm out of mana.
I shouldn't be spamming it like that, actually.
I can't be building like this.
I need to get rid of these.
Do I have a better weapon than that?
Let me actually equip my...
thingy.
This one.
That way I'm gonna use...
Do I have mana potions on me, though?
Mana?
I do, okay.
Wasn't there also an item that I could put up?
Oh wait, I can just pick these up, of course.
That's how I'm gonna get mana.
Hey! Out of my house!
Out of my damn house!
Oh, recall potion. Oh, cool.
I wonder if I actively attack these guys, if it will stop quicker.
I'm getting a lot of money.
Hey!
Did I do it?
They're definitely dropping in frequency.
Right?
Look, there's almost nobody left.
Oh, I know what this bottom part of the house can be, by the way.
It can be, like, similar to the Minecraft house I had, where I had the outside portion of my house with the bricks on the floor.
But it had, like, an overhang, you know? It had the house above it, but it was still outside.
That's what this is gonna be, like a little work area.
I like the sound of that.
Get away!
Can it curve enough to go up? Okay, yeah.
Nice.
What did I get?
Kill Pinky.
What? Did I kill a special slime?
This one? There's someone over here.
Three gold.
Damn!
Oh!
Yo, what's up with the...
Okay, nevermind.
I thought I got way more gold than I did just now.
It's accumulating when I walk over it.
It's not three gold, three gold, three gold, three gold.
Oh, wait a minute.
A slime banner.
I should totally place that.
This is, like, the time to have a slime banner.
Holy crap.
I wonder how much extra damage I do now.
One-shot him now.
It was two-shot before, I believe, so this is a big upgrade.
150th green slime.
And notice, that's just the green one.
Please stop now.
No more.
I kind of want to just fish while this is going on and let my minions take care of it.
Honestly, it's not that powerful, unfortunately.
I'm actually getting a lot of money from this.
I have, like, 70 as well in my piggy bank.
Oh!
King Slime has awoken!
Where?
Oh my god, here we go.
This is how... it's happening.
Uh...
Uh, I don't have time for this.
Drink, uh, drink, just drink all the things.
Oh my god.
Ja!
Okay, let's not go too crazy here.
Hello.
Let me laser you.
There's a guy inside!
There's a guy inside him, look!
Oh my god.
I'm taking damage.
Take care of this.
Oh!
He appeared right on me.
Okay, let's focus here.
He's going to teleport and I have to be ready.
There we go!
Oh god.
Okay, that wasn't too bad, holy shit!
Samson!
Uh, hold on, my inventory is full.
Deposit all.
Oh ho.
King slime trophy!
A treasure bag.
Oh.
Slimes become friendly?
Fuck yeah!
Solidifier.
Hold on now.
Slime hook?
Yo.
How much better?
Uh, is that better?
That doesn't feel better.
No, it's not.
But maybe it has a different effect?
Hold on.
No, it's a hook.
It's worse.
Wait a minute, what do you mean no stats will be gained?
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, I see.
So I needed...
Ah, that's too bad.
Hmm.
Well, it's very nice to have when you're building.
If you don't want things to annoy you all the time.
A ninja shirt.
Ninja pants.
I need the last part of that.
Hold on.
Was there more being dropped over here than I missed?
Also, what's Samson?
Caplook!
You get petted.
Okay, well, King Slime.
Fuck yeah, man.
Dude, my inventory is horrendous.
I can't.
I have to go back and fix this right now.
I'm losing my damn mind.
I can't, I can't.
We have to fix this immediately.
Click that button.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Chisel.
Open this.
Whoa!
Equip a mount.
How?
Wait, there was a keybind for that.
Quick mount.
Oh, it's...
Oh!
Yo, what?
Wait, really?
I mean, it's not super fast, but you can jump hella high.
I can't fly, though, in this state, but I can do this.
So, what I can do...
Hold on a second.
What if I...
Okay, no.
I can't keep doing that back and forth.
That would be crazy, though.
Okay, interesting.
I wonder if this will let me float on water.
I have to try that immediately.
No, no, no, no, no.
Inventory first.
And then we try it.
Don't get distracted now.
We gotta try the inventory.
Management.
But hold on, before we do it, let me quickly check if the trees are growing.
Ayy!
It's working!
Nice!
And quickly, let me try and put one in between these two.
To see if that will grow later on.
It's an experiment.
One, two, three, four.
No, they can definitely be closer, like that.
So, that's like... wait a minute.
One, two, three, four.
Yo.
Oh, wait, there's stuff here.
Unpleasant harp.
Yo.
Yo, what the fuck?
Uh...
Where's the harpoon?
Ah.
Okay.
I guess that was from... well, the goblins I killed.
Dude, I like how I said I'm gonna chillax today.
This is gonna be a chill stream and I've done nothing but fighting almost.
Because the game forces it on me.
Look at the background.
We have the lanterns now, because we did our deed.
How are you liking this new place?
I have no idea how I got here, but it's Mega Rat.
Yay!
I absolutely love having my own place to be myself.
This is like totally awesome.
I love animals, so naturally the forest is like the best place ever.
Dude, am I just... the shit or what, huh?
Look what I did here.
Also, let me put on my stuff again.
I kinda look like a silly boy.
By the way, this right here, the Kingslam trophy, definitely goes in the desert house.
As a memory of what we have achieved in that place.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Armor and stuff like that goes...
I mean, I guess in here, but I don't have any more space.
So let's put it in here.
It's very random.
Yeah, I should have put this stuff here instead of...
I don't know why I did it like this.
Whatever.
This can be sold.
The tool belts, I think I wanna equip that.
Silver ore?
Plop.
Put stuff in.
The slime hook, honestly, I'm gonna sell it.
Because it's not a material and it kinda sucks.
Oh, no, no, the wooden beam.
Let's put that back.
Plop.
We have one wooden beam in this entire house.
I don't know.
That's funny to me.
We have two wooden doors.
See, the wooden doors, they can stay here.
I'm not gonna use wood over there.
Purple slime banner.
I wish that was just a slime banner. Like, come on.
You really have to put a slime for every color.
That's a bit too much, isn't it?
Green one I have already deleted.
These ones I can bring.
Now, this one I also wanna sell.
Take this, please.
I feel like, if anything, the dive-at needs to be bought and placed in the desert house.
Because that's where Hano's gonna be.
And it fits, I think.
You know?
Potion of return.
Let's put this stuff in here.
No, put it in...
Actually, I have so much bullshit here.
Loot all.
Like that.
And...
Honestly, all the potions go in here.
Like, everyone.
Ah, maybe not the recall.
There we go.
Anything else?
These ones I keep, I believe, because this is used in combat.
Gimme this, that.
Okay, now click that.
And the black lens...
I think I have one of those already.
Or maybe not, it didn't stack to anything.
When I clicked on the button, so...
Can you tell me about this?
Whoa!
Optic staff!
Oh, 24 summon damage!
Ah, I need soul of sight.
I have no idea what that is.
Crap.
Yeah.
The essence of omniscient watchers.
So, I guess I need to kill omniscient watchers somewhere.
Mithril anvil!
Ah-ha!
Alright.
Weapons? Oh, man.
Ah, these chests are getting full!
Oh, this is the second weapon chest I have, I guess.
Yeah, let's put it in here.
This one as well.
This one I want to keep.
Slow sticks.
Man, I spent so much time managing inventory in this game.
I wish I could spend less time on it.
Because it's really taking up a lot of time.
Like, I know exactly what I want to do with all these things.
I just... it's a chore to get through.
You know? Put them where they need to be.
This potion goes in here.
Ice block.
The ice stuff we can save for later. We don't need to have that on us right now.
Magellani is in there.
Sand block, I want to... actually, do I have any more sand?
At all.
I do not.
Third block, put it in.
This one also...
You know what? Put it in here.
And this one as well.
I will sell this one.
By the way, I was thinking, if I'm going to make my magic missile my main weapon,
I don't really need this armor outfit.
Because the set bone is a space gun.
It does have increased magic damage, which does help my magic missile.
But maybe there's another armor set that will help my magic missile in different ways as well.
On top of this.
So I need to experiment with that. That's what I'm saying here.
Paintings go in.
Tables go in.
And Hano...
You need to buy this one.
And that one. Sure, why not?
Last wall. I'll keep that.
So, some of these I don't use.
Actually, I use most of them.
Although, honestly, this one, I don't really use that.
Maybe I should stop wearing it.
Man, it feels wrong, but I'm going to unequip it.
Isn't that crazy?
This feels illegal to do.
Oh my god, this is so illegal.
We didn't even put this here, man.
Oh my goodness.
These are the three potions I use all the time.
The glow sticks.
Let's put them in the miscellaneous for now.
Okay.
Alright.
Inventory fixed.
And this one is also almost fixed.
Pretty much. I'm going to keep the stone.
Alright, let's continue.
I need to figure out a way to plant...
Oh, you know what, actually?
I could buy planters for Sakura trees and stuff, right?
Maybe I can buy similar planters for palm trees.
That's probably how I do that.
I just need to find the right vendor.
So, here's my plan.
This bottom part here...
We're actually...
Yeah, I do want to...
There we go.
I do want to have the brick wall down here.
Like a nice background, I guess.
Oh, I need to make more.
Sandstone.
Excuse me.
No, no.
There we go.
Nice.
And then this part right here has the smooth sandstone wall.
Look at how we change it up.
Isn't that beautiful?
Well, honestly, it looks like...
No.
Looks like a place where Jabba the Hutt lives.
Actually, I hate it.
I take it back.
We need a different wall.
Let's make wall out of the limited amount of...
Palm wood we have.
Let's see here.
Wood wall, palm... yeah, palm wood wall.
Oh yeah, that's it. That's what I'm talking about.
Already much better.
Oh, okay.
I defeated a vulture.
Look at that.
Maybe I will remove the bottom part.
And the top part...
Sure.
I'm gonna have windows as well, of course.
Do I have enough?
I think I do.
Nice.
Nothing else that's missing? Oh no.
Shit.
No!
There we go.
Okay, not too shi- oh wait, I'm missing a couple parts.
Okay!
This looks weird.
The way the transition there is.
In fact, it looks so weird that I don't like it.
No, that's not what I want.
Oh my god.
And in this bottom part here, I'm actually gonna remove the wall.
Ah, it's gonna take a while.
Oh yeah, much better. Look at this.
This looks cool.
We can even have a couple more pillars on the bottom there.
There we go.
Nice.
That's cool.
Pillars?
Something like that.
Look at that.
Beautiful stuff right there.
Oh my god, look at all the money down here.
My minion has been busy.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I have to remember, my weapon is now on a new keybind.
That's gonna take some time getting used to.
Get out of here.
Okay.
And then...
Let's make like...
No!
Stupid ass smart cursor, you're not smart at all, you suck.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know. I'm embarrassing here.
Yo, I wonder.
Oh, wait, do I have no more windows?
No way.
I think I need a furnace to make more...
Wait, did I really...
Did I use it all?
Anyway, let me try something.
No, I can't make the window slanted, I don't think.
Not looking good.
I need more sand.
Give me sand.
But I think if I move sand, it's gonna not look as nice.
Maybe I'll take sand from the pool here.
Or on the other side.
Yeah, let's take sand from over here.
Let's make a nice little hole.
Give me sand block.
Not the sand.
And then I believe we can craft a furnace.
Yep.
Oh, wait.
Why can I not place...
This is a background.
Huh?
Maybe it's not technically a background.
That's a bit weird.
But okay.
And then with this furnace, I can make glass, right?
Because I have sand.
Oh, but wait a minute.
Wasn't there something like...
Is this what I've been using?
Wait a minute.
Oh yeah, it is, it is. Okay, okay.
Perfect.
There we go, there we go.
Not too shabby.
Let me make this a bit more.
How nice and bright this looks now.
Maybe even have a little balcony or something.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Let's make a balcony.
Maybe not out of platform.
That doesn't look too bad, actually.
The smooth sandstone?
Pretty dope.
You know what?
Let's make this part out of smooth sandstone.
It's like the foundational part.
Not too shabby.
Oh yeah, I don't have to remove it first. I have to remember this.
Yeah!
Hey, that's kind of cool.
And then...
Where's the nice looking one?
Can I sort please?
Like that.
And...
Yeah. And we need a door.
A vulture banner.
I mean, sure.
This is the place to hang it, I guess.
The trophy for King Slime.
Right there.
Actually, put it here instead.
No, I like it here. I like it there.
It's a good place.
Cactus lantern?
There we go.
A little working light.
And now we can craft sand things.
Look at this.
Sandstone door.
Oh, we need to make a bit more.
There we go.
Yeah!
Cool.
What else?
A sandstone lantern.
Let's have a working light outside here, like that.
Oh my goodness.
Actually, have it on the other side, because there's already light here.
Sort of.
There.
We can hang these here, I guess.
Like that.
This is starting to look like something.
This will be two rooms.
What else can I craft here?
Let's make a lamp.
And a table.
Oh, a nice looking sandstone chair.
Let's make two tables, actually.
And...
candelabra.
Candle.
Let's see here.
There we go.
What's this there?
Yeah, that's a very small chair.
But I guess it has no back support.
That works.
I guess.
A table there.
Let's put a little candle on top of that table.
Look at how nice that looks.
And a lamp.
Put that there.
Very cool.
And we also have this one.
Maybe I'll put that there instead.
It's a bit more flashy.
There's a little candle in the corner there.
I can't put it.
Maybe there's not enough room there.
I don't like this lamp.
This lamp goes away.
I like this, though.
There.
Look at this!
Huh?
Not bad at all.
One more of that, and then some more gold.
Last one.
There.
I'm so focused right now, dude.
Something like that.
What else can I make?
I have a door.
That's good enough, I guess, for now.
I also have a bunch of decorative stuff back at home and put here.
This is a good start, though.
No, I could make a fence, no?
Fence, fence, fence.
Can I not make a...
Wooden fence? Can I make a sandstone fence?
Or something like it?
I need to make a little railing up here so people don't fall off, you know?
Monsters are out.
So what exactly is this little thing here?
I guess I can craft certain things with it.
But I don't know what those things are yet.
Make a pink torch.
Actually, Tiki torch.
Hey!
Yo!
I like that.
Look at this.
It's starting to look like something.
Now I want to go like this, and then we say Hano.
Also, are these houses suitable?
Suitable.
Hano.
There you go.
You get to be up here.
You get the big one.
Please let me work.
And then the other one is Dante.
You get to be there.
This is now Hano and Dante's place.
Done.
Feels good, man.
Oh, it seems like they already moved in.
What's up, guys? Do you like this place?
This is what I'm talking about.
Privacy.
You know, the desert is secluded and great for business if you catch my drift.
I... no, I don't.
That makes no fucking sense.
But, sure, man.
Whatever floats your boat.
Hano.
My dear, this place is quiet enough.
This palace is quiet enough to sleep like a sultan.
The desert is really nice.
Reminds me of my hometown. I like it very much so.
Dante the Arms Dealer has good eyes for vividness in business.
I like it, yes.
Dude, they love it. They're loving the shit.
Desert pylon.
Teleport to another pylon when two villagers are nearby.
You can only place...
What?
Haven't I seen one of these before?
I have memories of reading this at some point.
Oh!
Wait!
Oh my god!
Oh wait, did we just discover...
Wait, why do I have two of these now?
Eh?
Did I just duplicate it?
Did I just... bug abuse?
Where should I put it?
Oh my god.
Wait a minute.
Can I make one at my house?
Hold on guys, I'll be back.
I have more.
But it's a desert pylon.
I can only place it in the matching biome.
Okay, so I need a forest pylon.
Okay.
Are you selling it?
No, wait.
Seymour.
How? Wait, why did he suddenly have the pylon?
That's what I don't understand here.
I don't think these guys...
Hmm.
Edmond?
Pink?
Ella?
So, you can teleport to another pylon when two villagers are nearby.
Does that mean minimum two or exactly two?
Because if that's the case, then I think I understand.
Oh, I'm sorry, squirrel.
I think I blasted off to heaven.
I apologize.
God damn.
Man, what a big house we have here.
I was so not used to this after being over there now for a bit.
Yeah, this place is big.
Maybe Fjell has one.
He's like a tingerer, right?
He would have one.
No, he totally doesn't.
And I'm speaking of Fjell.
Hold on.
This crowding triggers bad memories of goblin war camps.
I really hate it.
Ella, the mechanic makes my cardiac core function improperly.
It appears I love how that feels.
Wait, you love Ella.
Hold on, Fjell?
Fjell, you hate crowding.
So, minus people.
Plus Ella.
Everyone hates crowding.
Except the party girl, I guess.
Wow, Oliver, meeting an adventurous man like you makes me want to party.
Is there anything in this world that doesn't make you want to party?
It's my question.
There's so many people here.
I hate that it's not for a party.
I think Seymour the Merchant is a killjoy at parties.
Wait, what?
I hate that it's not.
Okay, so you only like parties.
Is that your whole thing?
That's the only thing you want, is party.
Well...
I hate parties.
Well, some parties.
Did you know I have three amazingly awesome fish now?
That's because as far as errant monkeys go, you're actually a bit useful.
Wait, he's keeping track?
I hate strangers.
They scare all my fish half to death.
Sparkle actually knows what they're doing, unlike some other people.
I kind of like that. Okay, so hold on, Izzy.
You like Sparkle?
Party?
Maybe I should start calling them by their type of NPC instead of name,
because they will maybe get replaced later.
You like that? Okay.
Mortal knows what they're doing, so you like him.
Demo guy.
I kind of like that.
I hate Drisken.
Okay.
Got it.
You hate Drisken.
That's good.
Thank you for that information.
Lion!
You keep swinging like that, you'll end up hurting someone or yourself.
Hate to say it.
But I'd rather hate all the foot traffic here.
I like the forest.
It has all the necessary features for golfing.
It's always fun to hang out with Ludo the Painter.
Okay, hold on.
Golfer?
Plus Painter?
Okay.
Unpopular opinion.
I love Izzy.
Oh, okay, cool.
You guys are going together then.
Hopefully Izzy loves you too.
I hate Seymour.
Okay.
These guys are so needy.
Alright, I get my water hazards returned to me.
It's pretty unnecessary in a world like this.
Greedy attitude, okay.
You hate all the foot traffic.
You want to be alone, you want to be with the Painter and Izzy.
Gotcha.
Soggy.
Pedem.
Okay.
Triskin.
Not sure I like living next door to so many people.
Mortall the Demolitionist is one crazy little drinker.
I love it.
Okay.
So you are Taren Keep.
Taren Man.
Minus people.
Everyone hates people.
You like Mortall.
Gotcha.
Thank you for that information.
I'll be moving on.
Katlyn.
That's not the biggest I've ever seen.
Yes, I've seen bigger wounds for sure.
Mm-hmm.
Ugh!
I hate how unhealthy it is to cram so many people in one place.
I don't like sparkle the party girl that much.
It kind of weirds me out.
Yeah.
I got I get that.
So you just want to be alone, huh?
You just want to be alone.
You don't want to be with anybody?
Who do you like to be with?
You just don't want to be with her. Okay.
Well, all right.
You really want to be alone?
Don't you want to heal people?
That's...
I wish Mortall would be more careful in getting tired of having to sew his limbs back on every day.
That makes sense.
Maybe you don't like Mortall.
Bradley, how would it happen is for you.
I'm quite fond of wandering through the forest.
I like it here.
I'm quite fond of Edmund the Clothier.
We have a lot in common.
Yes, you do.
You both have creepy-ass dolls made of you.
And a voodoo cursed cast upon you, it seems.
You guys are weirdos.
You get to stay here.
And Ella.
What did I write about her?
Minus Edmund plus Viel.
Less people.
All right, all right, all right.
So let's see, who should I put together here?
The golfer with the painter and Izzy.
Who's the painter?
Do I have a painter?
Ludo, of course.
Ludo!
I hope it doesn't rain again until this paint dries.
That would be a disaster.
Okay.
I hate noisy crowds.
When will I get some peace and quiet?
Why don't I light the forest?
Because it's boring.
Green, brown, that's it.
Sparkle, the party girl and I like the same shade of pink.
That's a friend in my book.
Well...
Okay.
So you two should hang out.
And, hold on.
Wait a minute.
So Ludo likes Sparkle.
Uh, Sparkle just wants to...
Hold on.
I need to remember this.
You hate...
Okay.
Did I actually write this down?
I didn't.
Uh, party girl.
You hate Seymour.
Minus merchant.
Okay.
So I'm gonna put party girl with Ludo.
And...
Someone also liked the party girl.
Izzy.
So Izzy,
Painter,
Golfer,
and Sparkle.
Is what I'm getting here.
Oh my god.
No, no, wait, the Golfer wants to be in the forest.
Jesus fuck, this is getting complicated, man.
Are you kidding me?
So you don't wanna...
Okay.
Sparkle doesn't care, I guess, where she is.
So Ludo and...
Let me actually write that.
Ludo and Sparkle go together.
So Painter,
plus Sparkle.
Okay.
Those are confirmed being together now.
And Izzy,
did you have a biome preference?
You don't.
Alright, so Izzy comes with them.
They go together for now.
And I guess it doesn't matter where.
Actually, the Painter doesn't wanna be in the forest.
So anywhere but the forest.
Right?
Okay, good.
Let's make something anywhere but the forest.
How about the jungle?
Yeah.
Let's make a jungle house.
Let's make it...
over here.
Hell yeah, dude.
Can I now do this?
You're not close enough to a pylon.
Okay, okay.
I need to somehow get a pylon here.
Actually, hold on, see more.
Okay.
I guess I can test now as well whether or not
this will actually work the way I think.
Because if I make three people move in together,
will I be able to get a pylon or not?
From the description, it kinda sounds like you need two.
And not more.
Oh, hold on.
I spoke to Hanno.
He sold me the...
Wait.
He sold me desert pylon?
Will you also sell me?
Ah, you also do. Okay.
So anyone who can shop will be able to give me the option, I guess.
If I fulfill the requirements.
Let's make a journey.
Ah, carve a path through all this.
Almost there.
You know, it would be kinda cool to have a house inside of here.
A jungle house inside of a cave.
Let's fucking do it.
So hold on, jungle stuff.
Wait, am I in the jungle?
No, wait a minute, this...
Oh no, wait, this is the same as this?
This is like that special jungle.
That's not really a jungle.
This is the jungle.
We need to keep going.
Look at the trees here.
I think we've got a...
We've got a no jungle here.
This is a no jungle.
I freaking love how people took that shit to heart, man, and embraced that meme.
Okay, um...
Let's find a good place for this.
Oh!
We're fine.
God, this is gonna be annoying.
Hey, wait a minute!
Slimes, why are you not friendly?
Oh wait, they are friendly.
Imp, will you stop?
Listen, Imp, we are friends with these guys now.
Was that a fly just hitting me?
Whatever.
Alright, the slime's not gonna hurt me.
I wanna make the house...
Oh wait, I'm in water.
Let's not drown here.
What's happening?
Where am I?
Oh, I'm stuck on a little piece of geometry there.
Weird.
I might remember when I made this.
I was trying to fish here.
Okay, so...
I have an idea here.
For a house.
I have a great idea.
Is this just dirt?
What is this?
It's mud, okay, okay.
Yeah, alright.
I need more mud.
Oh man, look at this nice little waterfall here too.
This is neat.
Here we go.
What is this?
Jungle wood?
Oh, it's rich mahogany.
Just deposit that for now.
I think I have enough.
Wait...
Wait a minute, what did I wanna do here?
I forgot not how.
Right, remove this.
Give me that sweet, sweet mahogany.
And now we're gonna...
Wait, didn't I get more mud?
Gosh, let me get some mud down here.
Look at them, they're not damaging me at all.
This is actually such a great item.
And one of this items will work on the King's Lime.
That would be a little OP, wouldn't it?
But I guess...
Probably not.
That would be too OP.
Actually...
On my ultimate plan here, I'm actually gonna remove two layers here.
Just wait till you see what I've got cooking here.
Water's coming out of this somehow.
Water.
So man, rich mahogany, I gotta make it out of that?
Gotta...
Gotta make it out of that.
I'll have to figure out how to plant more of these later.
Give me the rich mahogany.
I could also make it...
bamboo stuff.
Do I wanna make bamboo stuff?
Dude!
I totally wanna make bamboo stuff.
Yikes!
Recall.
I think I have bamboo.
Yeah!
I also have cactus!
I guess cactus is not really needed right now.
Although it is needed.
It's actually not needed.
Is it?
Maybe it's not needed.
We don't need cactus.
Hey?
Okay.
Hold on now.
Who just...
Who sold me...
the planters for the different trees?
I believe it was Hayley, actually.
Hold on.
Hayley!
Tell me.
I may not know, like, a whole lot, but I can talk your head off about nature and critters and animals and wildlife and...
Willow.
Sakura.
Dark horse mount.
Flamingo.
No, it doesn't look like you have any...
Then again, hold on now.
Rosalva.
Let's quickly visit Rosalva.
Let's see what she has to sell.
I guess I need to have someone else move in with her.
Man, I'm so proud of this little place.
Why does Seymour keep trying to sell me angel statues?
Everyone knows that they don't do anything.
But now that you say that, are you actually sure?
Solitude is sometimes good. There's room to grow and to breathe. Okay.
Let's see here.
Tall grass, wild... wild... acorn... pumpkin seeds.
These are all flowers.
Shiverthorn.
Shit.
Prevent you from accidentally destroying the environment while in the inventory.
This is something I don't understand.
I don't get that.
What does that even mean? Why?
So I need to have the inventory open and then when I fight in combat or I remove blocks,
I'm not destroying the... what?
I guess I need to... I have one of these at home.
Fuck, okay.
So I need someone else to live here as well.
You know what? Let's continue that while we're here.
Let's make a second... let's a little room up. There's a guest room up there.
Look at this.
This is a little bit scuffed, but it is what it is.
We're gonna have a little guest room up here.
That looks fucking hilarious.
Let's see here.
Can I make a rich mo... I don't know. No, no, no, no. I just want regular wood. I don't even...
I don't even have that.
Wait, I can...
Oh, I can make wood out of...
Oh, sure. Let's make a bit.
You can go back and forth between these two. That's kind of awesome.
Let's have a table and a chair.
Let's also have a light.
I guess we have a light.
Oh, but wait, it needs a wall.
It needs a wall. Let's see here.
It's gonna be a mud wall.
Or like a dirt wall.
Do I have dirt?
I need to find some dirt.
There's dirt everywhere, I guess.
Let me grab some of this dirt.
Oh!
Give me dirt.
That should be enough.
Let's make a dirt wall here.
I kind of like the rugged look of that.
Dirt wall.
Oh, it already was dirt wall. Okay, perfect.
Let's remove that little piece there.
Have a little torch there.
Is this room suitable?
Will this do?
Oh no, you need a wall.
But hold on, will dirt work?
Oh no, I guess not, right?
Wait, isn't this a wall? Hold on.
There's like... oh wait, what did I just... no, no, no, no, no.
Wood.
Yeah, maybe I do need to make wood all around it.
But that's okay.
I'm keeping the aesthetic of the environment that's already here.
I don't want to change it.
It's beautiful the way it is.
It's missing a wall. Really? Where?
Where is it missing a wall?
Are you kidding?
Make some more wall like this.
Or a roof, I guess, there.
How is this not a wall?
It's all surrounded.
Huh?
I don't get it.
What the fuck?
Is it the platform?
Let me try something.
Why does this not work?
Oh my god, I'm an idiot, it says wall.
Oh my fucking god.
Something's missing somewhere here.
Now?
Huh?
What am I missing? Is it...
Hold on.
Maybe...
Maybe there's like a little piece that's...
It's placing things.
Oh my god!
Wait a minute, is this the same?
Wait, I don't understand what's happening.
Ah, okay, there we go, there we go.
That was weird.
I have no idea why that...
It's suitable.
There we go.
There we go!
Okay.
Let's see here.
Who could be here?
Let's see.
Maybe...
Edmond?
Maybe Edmond.
Who liked Edmond?
Let's see here.
Edmond, Edmond.
Hold on, Edmond is the Clothier.
Can you please stop making noise?
Fuck off.
Let me think.
Who should I send here?
Let me actually just do something.
Let's bring Mortal.
He likes Drisken, he likes Ella.
He hates Dante and he hates Phil.
Very specific, that guy.
Fuck it, let's bring him here.
Oh, but he likes those two people, so I should probably put him with him.
Are you fucking for real right now?
Rosalba?
What did you just do?
Eh?
So two goblins walk into a bar and one says to the other,
want to get a goblet of beer?
Wow, that's such a good one.
Nice one.
Alright, Rosalba is doing something that I don't quite understand.
Fuck, I don't know what to bring here, dude.
I'm looking at my notes here.
We could bring the Tavernkeep.
No, he likes Mortal.
No, Hanoi, we already did place somewhere.
Let's bring Edmond here.
Fuck it.
Edmond, where you at?
There you are.
Are you gonna sell me something?
Hold on, let's wait a bit here, see if he arrives.
Let's see what happens now.
Maybe we do need to move away first.
Oh yeah, look, we have to be out of the screen.
He's here now.
In the guest room.
Aha! Wait, Cavernpylon!
Oh! Wait, how are you liking this place?
I'm not a popular man, but I know what tranquility is.
Seeing is believing, but sometimes the most likeable things are in the underground.
So you like it!
You two can hang out. Here's the thing. Edmond is kind of a piece of shit.
You know? He's mysterious, he's kind of creepy, he's nasty.
Nobody likes him.
So we hide him away in this little hidey hole down here.
Where Rosalva, who's a saint, can take care of him. Nobody else has to.
There it is.
He stays here.
And we are gonna purchase a Cavernpylon.
But here's the thing.
If we want to be smart about this, we should maybe separate them a little bit.
You know?
I could even have some really deep underground.
We could make a whole network of pylons.
That wouldn't be too shabby.
But for now, I guess it's fine to have it here.
We can always move it around later.
This is a good first starting point.
Wait, you're not actually gonna sell me.
It's only Edmond.
Ha!
Okay.
All right.
So what I'm gonna do here is the following.
I will...
excavate a little bit over here.
Where is it?
There it is.
Where's my... there.
I wanna make more than one wall.
I can make a rich mahogany wall too. I wonder what that looks like.
I'll never find out!
Here.
Beautiful stuff.
Absolutely beautiful.
I guess that works.
And we're gonna have a little door.
And that's it.
Look at that!
We have a little room just for the pylon.
What do you think about that?
Huh?
I think it's pretty neat.
I don't like the way this looks though.
What is this background?
Right here.
Oh no.
What is this background?
I don't know.
Fuck it, this is all dirt now.
This is the dirt part where it starts.
And then we have this.
Or even better.
This room gets to be wood.
Let's make it super fancy.
Look at this shit, man.
So nice!
I have a torch in there.
There.
Beautiful stuff.
And that's how we're gonna teleport around.
Plop!
Fantastic.
Isn't that great?
Can I keep doing this forever?
Oh my god.
That is incredible.
I feel like I should have done this earlier.
But of course, I didn't know about it earlier.
Alright then.
Very nice.
Here's the thing I wanna do though.
Remember the magic liquid we found last time?
I actually wanna go back there real quick.
And try fishing in it.
I can't believe I didn't think about that last time.
But it's something I thought about yesterday.
Like why didn't I think about that?
Obviously I'm gonna try and fish in that liquid.
What the fuck?
Where is it?
Now we have to play the game of where did I put my fishing pole?
It's gonna take a while I guess.
Oh, probably in the fishing chest.
Yes, I'm so good.
Well done me.
I need some bait now.
Let's take apprentice.
Master enjoyment.
Those are the three magic.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, there.
Let's look at the water.
Because I seem to remember something about a box.
And the potion.
Bradley!
We talked about this earlier or actually we didn't.
That was the other guy.
But tell me about the potions.
There's a fishing one.
Fishing.
Wait, fishing power.
Yo, straight up.
Crisp.
Okay, I don't have that crispy honey block.
All right, that sounds intriguing though.
I'll check that out later.
Wait, where is it?
Motherfucker.
Where is it?
Mining heart reach.
Gradle lock.
What the fuck?
Where is it?
There was a potion of increased chance of finding a crate.
Crate potion.
Amber.
Water leaf.
Shiverthorn.
Oh, I think I have all that.
This is a lot to remember.
Amber.
Moonglow.
Shiverthorn.
Water leaf.
Gems.
Oh, I can only make four.
That's fine.
Let's see if I remember all this.
Moonglow.
Water leaf.
And...
Shiverthorn.
Was that it?
Let's see.
Yeah!
Make them all.
Ah, we made six because we're standing next to the table here,
which has a chance of not using ingredients.
Fantastic!
The money.
The money's not in here.
Why is the money not in here?
Eh?
Say what now?
Give me this, that, that, that, that, that.
Ah, yeah, sure, take that as well.
My inventory is full.
But that's okay.
Because I'm not building right now.
In this moment.
Organic.
Put this in here.
In there.
All right, let's go fish in that place.
And... ah, yeah.
Definitely the pylon here in the forest.
That's a must.
I need to figure out how to do that exactly.
Stop, oh my, this is so nice!
I love this little place here.
Where did I find the spot, by the way?
Oh my god, it's all the way over here.
Jeez, all the way over there, okay.
All right.
That's okay.
Maximum speed.
Actually, hold on, I'm gonna quickly...
I gotta take a piss real quick, be right back.
All right.
I have to say though, after playing this game for a while,
the sound effect of me getting hit is not as funny anymore as it was before.
I always laughed so much whenever I heard that sound effect,
and I never knew where it came from.
But now that I know, I feel like that meme has died a little bit for me.
You know, it's like, I'm so used to the sound now, novelty wore off.
And that's sad.
I guess it's still funny when you put it in memes,
but in the game it's like, it was funny at first in the game, you know.
No more.
Blop, blop, blop, blop, blop.
So this is the forest. Oh my god, what a forest it is.
This is the... jungle.
Dude, imagine, what if a meteor hits your home?
I wonder if that's possible.
What if a meteor falls directly on the community center that I made?
I wonder if that's even possible.
That would be funny.
Oh man, see, this is what we need to pile on all the way over here.
Maybe I should do that immediately.
Build something over there, let people move in and make a pile on.
I think I have to do that.
At the ocean, right?
It's not pleasing me.
I feel more pleased now.
Ah, here we go. We're about to approach a thingy.
Oh my god, I can gain some quick...
If I do it as smartly.
Hey, that was kind of sick.
What I just did there.
I feel like this should be the place for Izzy the Angler.
It's where I found him.
Izzy likes the painter.
Right?
You know what? Let's build a damn hut here.
Out of bamboo, huh?
Oh no, did I?
Crap, where's my... mud?
Bro, where's my sand? There.
Oh, I like this song.
This is a great song.
Oh, I know what to do here. I have an idea.
I have a great idea for a construction.
No. Oh, I have the wrong thing to put this in.
Oh, this is gonna be great.
Wait till you see this shit.
There's so many palm trees here. This is gonna be palm wood.
The base is palm wood.
Ah, let's see here.
Actually, place this back.
And now...
Where's my normal ass wood?
There it is. Palm wood.
Ah, palm wood, palm wood.
I'm gonna make...
Yeah, look at this.
I really like how this looks.
It pleases me greatly.
And this is what I had in mind. Check this out.
I'm gonna make a pier. From where we can fish, huh?
But I'm not sure if I'm gonna make it out of this or some other material.
I don't have any pillars on me anymore, but I can probably make a palm wood pillar.
Let's see here.
Bamboo.
Palm wood wall is what I will need.
Palm wood door.
Oh wait, I needed a...
sawmill for that, didn't I?
Fuck.
Something like that, at least.
I needed a different one. Or was it a heavy workbench? I forgot.
How do I even make that?
Alright.
For now, we're just gonna keep it simple, I guess.
Good source of potassium.
Increases life regeneration.
Nice.
Seashell.
Alright, well I'm just gonna keep it simple for now.
There we go.
I need two people living here. So let me actually make it super simple. This is temporary.
It's all super temporary. Super duper duper temporary.
Hahaha.
Oh yeah baby.
I need doors. Palm doors.
Give me three.
Uno dos tres.
And then, banana gets consumed.
Because we are in the desert, damn it. We gotta eat bananas.
There we go.
And there we go.
Remove that, I don't like it.
And it's time for wall.
But not just any wall.
Ultra special, magnificent wall.
Palm of the wall.
Do I already have that though?
Did I leave that at home?
Shit.
This is not enough, is it?
That looks nice.
Nice!
Ah, I have a little bit...
Okay, delete it.
I know it's waste. Look at all the crabs!
The crabs are having a dance party out here.
This is like that meme with the crabs dancing on the beach.
You know what I mean.
Plop in the water you go.
And in the water you go.
Oh, look at that, that looked nice with the way that it was lighting up the water there.
Fuck off, I.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Now we need a table and some chairs.
But not just any table.
A palm wood workbench table.
On one side.
And on the other side, we're gonna have a palm wood table.
Plop.
Let's also have some chairs.
Two of them, in fact.
Why does it look like a plinth?
Oh, I don't have any clothes.
Remove that one.
This looks nice.
Let's have a campfire out here.
It looks super nice.
And lights we have, tables we have.
This should be fun, this should be a home.
Suitable, suitable.
Nice!
You fucker, you get to be there.
Even though I hate you.
Uh, Izzy goes with...
Let's say the painter.
Who dat?
Oh, it's not gonna reach it.
Alright.
Gimme that, gimme that.
Okay.
They should be moving in as soon as I...
Let me actually try something.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait for it.
Okay, no.
Wait, wait, wait, okay.
See, now they're there. Okay, okay, I see.
I was trying to get them to spawn because when I zoom in, they're technically out of the screen.
Look at them!
Tell me!
Oh no, they don't sell it.
No, no, no, there's tons of different greys.
Don't get me started.
This serene living space has all the quiet I need to focus on my mural.
Okay, so you're happy?
Yes!
I get to be alone with all my fish.
Why is the ocean my favorite place to go?
It has tons of cool fish, duh.
See, that's what I thought.
That's what I thought.
But Ludo, you...
Ludo, you're out of here.
You're gone.
Who else wanted to be with Izzy?
Let's see.
The golfer.
But he needed to be in the forest, no?
Because of golfing.
Who could we put here?
Mortol, maybe.
Wait, did I already put Mortol somewhere?
Who's here?
Oh, that's Edmond, right.
Maybe Edmond would be the perfect place to put here, actually.
Ludo's just fucking off now.
I'm like, you're evicted.
And he just walks off.
He shoots paint gun.
Paintballs.
Let's see.
Let's put Mortol here.
Why not?
Mortol.
Let me see if I recognize the icon.
Should be there.
No, that's Dante.
Ah, where is he?
There we go.
How about that?
Is that gonna work?
Let's see.
Moving.
There he is.
Okay, Mortol, tell me everything.
No, he still doesn't.
Are you happy here?
Ah, no one around.
I can test new bombs without creating a graveyard for limbs.
I can't stand the ocean.
My fuses have trouble igniting here.
Okay, so...
Mortol!
You're evicted.
Fuck off.
Let's try something else.
Catalan!
She didn't have any needs.
Right?
No, no, no.
Oh, but hold on.
People really wanted to be with Catalan.
At least some people.
So, let's see here.
What about Sparkle?
You two are very annoying together.
Let's see if this works.
There we go.
Sparkle?
I can't decide what I like more.
Parties or after parties?
Is this all mine?
I'm gonna throw the biggest party for myself.
Okay, what do you sell?
Are you selling what I need?
God damn it, why isn't it working?
Party wagon.
Maybe she needs to be happy.
Maybe she needs a party.
Bill is a fog.
Fuck, I don't know.
Let's try someone else.
What about...
Fjell?
Hold on, Fjell?
Liked Ella.
Doesn't like people.
But he didn't mention Izzy, so...
Did Izzy mention though?
He likes the Demolitionist.
Hates Driskin.
Actually likes Sparkle.
So these two go well together.
Let's try and add a third.
Let's try adding Fjell here.
He can be above.
Or actually... No, no!
Fjell is like a tinkerer, right?
He shall be in the basement.
We're gonna have a little basement here.
This is gonna be so sick.
Oh yeah, look at this.
It's already satisfying.
Wait, is this falling sand?
Oh yeah, it is.
Good thing water doesn't come through here, huh?
Something like that.
And then let's use a palm.
Ah, I think it's fine.
Give me that.
Platform?
Oh, I don't have enough.
Give me some more palm wood platform.
Here we are.
And now we have some wall.
Now I can use this again.
Delete that, I guess.
Delete the mud as well.
And the dirt.
Honestly, nah, this can stay.
These shells, I kinda wanna figure out what to do with them.
I gotta ask people.
Uh...
What just happened there?
Was that a star falling, or...?
Sea turtle!
Oh my god, I just had something in my mouth.
Uh, palm wood wall, maggots, please.
Palm wood...
Actually, do I want a different...
You know what, let's do sandstone down here.
Sandstone wall.
Ah, I had that at home.
Hey, sandstone brick wall!
Yay! That looks cool!
Dude!
Looks like a basement!
That looks super cool, man!
What the fuck?
Also, I have an idea.
Wait.
No, no, uh...
Oh!
Oh ho!
Can I fill that up with sand, though?
Alright, fine.
Doesn't work the way I thought it would work.
Alright, this still looks pretty fucking cool.
And you know what?
The workbench gets to be down there instead.
Because it's the tinkerer!
Uh, can we make a special...
Oh yeah, right.
Uh, make a normal table is what I meant to say.
There.
Give me the...
No!
By the way, is this...
There we go.
No!
Unequipped that, dammit!
There we go.
Workbench, here.
Make a little chair.
It's chair...
It's chair time!
There!
And then...
We should have a nice light.
Can I make a super nice light?
Oh wait, light is down here.
Uh, palm wood?
Yeah!
Oh!
Magnificent!
Is this suitable?
It's suitable!
And now...
Who did I want to bring?
Fjell!
Alright, Fjell!
This has to be it.
Uh...
Sparkle, don't jump!
Fjell!
Uh...
Why is he not appearing?
Let me move farther away.
Why is this not working?
No, no.
Hm.
Uh...
I'm not sure why this doesn't work.
What am I doing wrong?
Let's put someone else here, I guess.
Uh...
Mortal...
Uh, like Striskin and Ella.
Let's try Mortal here.
Mortal and these two.
Maybe that will work.
Mortal...
There.
Housing is...
Okay, weird.
Is he gonna spawn now?
Wait, what the fuck?
Wait, why is this not working anymore?
I have no idea what's happening.
Maybe they can only beat two people here at the beach for whatever reason.
Oh, look at that air balloon!
Anyway, I'm gonna try and make pillars for this here right now.
Pillars...
Let's see what I can make.
Ah, but wait, I needed a special ass crafting stuff for that, didn't I?
Actually, I wanna make one of these as well.
Look at that, that looks glorious.
Palmwood lamp as well.
Let's have that...
Let's remove this for a second.
There.
Let's have that lamp be...
And we can remove the torch.
Look at that, this looks way better.
Hey!
All three different types...
That's nice, isn't it?
We can even have a little window.
We get to look out now.
No windows down here, this is a basement.
Also, this chair can go somewhere else.
Put that chair in the corner there for some reason.
No, it doesn't look that good.
We put the chair back.
Is he gonna teleport now?
What?
I have no fucking clue why it doesn't work anymore.
What is happening?
Maybe there's a limit on how many you can teleport per time unit or something.
That's very weird.
Alright.
Well, whatever.
I wanted to go down here anyway and fish.
So let's try that now.
Everything's in order.
Whoa, what a throw.
Let's go down.
And let's equip something proper here.
So we're going down into the depths.
Where it's dangerous.
Do do do do.
Oh yeah, I made a thingy here.
Wait, why is the background not...
Huh. You don't? Okay.
So you only fall through when you are completely covered.
When it reaches your head in height, right?
Maybe I should have kept the slime thing equipped.
Shimmer slime. Wait a minute.
Did this just get transformed into a shimmer slime by being down here?
Hold on. Salamander, come here.
Oh, no, it fell down.
I actually hate this imp right now. Will you please fuck off?
They're so dumb, they fall down.
There you go. Come here.
Into the shimmer.
Black slime.
Shimmer slime.
Aha.
I wish he was... Okay.
Man, is there a way to dismiss summons?
It's actually pissing me off so much right now.
Doesn't look like it.
Fuck me. Alright, I'm gonna try fishing.
Oh no! Wait, what?
Why did I fall through?
Oh. Failing.
Oh, I'm... Hold on now.
Hold on, I'm going back up. Hold on, I'm not ready to... whatever this is.
Let me try this again. Was it because I was fishing?
Oh. Oh, yeah. Huh.
Isn't that interesting?
Weird.
Okay, so you cannot... Oh wait, this is maybe not the...
It's not deep enough anyway, I guess, for fishing. Hold on, we got a good...
It's so weird how I can walk up here, but not down.
Like, really?
That's so weird.
Okay.
Look at what I made here.
Let's not fall into it.
In fact, hold on. Let me think about this.
This is kind of a mess. I shouldn't have broken this right now, because it's kind of a mess to... fish.
Eh...
I guess I'll be removing some things.
Tell me here, do you have a... Whoops.
Where's my...
There. Beautiful.
That's what I needed. Oh, do you also have, perchance, a mining potion on you?
No. Alright, that's okay.
Here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna drain all this into... down here.
Basically.
So I can actually fish from it. Or not fish from it.
Hold on. Oh yeah, fish from it, yeah.
Don't break that yet.
Remove it in layers here.
Okay. I need some working lights. I love the background here.
You know what? We should make a house down here next to this.
This is actually so cool.
I wonder who would want to live here.
Hmm. Maybe I want to live here.
Maybe this is gonna be my home.
A cool ass underground cave.
But I guess I need other people to live here as well to have the pylon.
Right? So I need to think about who to bring.
Dude, I'm totally gonna bring the guide, of course.
It's gonna be the two of us. And maybe one more.
Oh, don't fall in, don't fall in.
Okay, I'm manualing now.
Oh, yeah, I'm equalizing it.
Listen to the sound.
Diamond! Oh, no!
Wait, what just happened?
Hold on.
Put it there.
Did something just happen to that?
It was a diamond. It got turned into a ruby.
Do I have more diamonds?
Wait.
What just happened there? It totally transformed it!
I'm not crazy, right?
That just happened.
I feel like I'm throwing coins in the wishing well right now.
Maybe it's only with gems?
This is kind of gemmy, isn't it? Almost.
Let's try...
Cactus candle.
Hey!
It disassembled it into its constituent parts.
Hold on now. So glass wall will become glass?
No way, Jose!
So wait, this should become wood.
Oh my god!
What about...
One potion.
Something's missing!
There were more ingredients in that potion.
Excuse me?
Hold on, how do I get there?
Moonglow wood.
Yeah, I didn't get everything back.
That potion needed four ingredients.
Remember?
So you don't get everything back.
Interesting.
I kind of want to throw a weapon in.
Well, it's just going to disassemble it, I guess.
What else can I throw in?
Let's actually throw one strange ruin there.
Aha!
So this one cannot be crafted.
That's what I'm getting from this. You can only get this in the wild.
What about one bottled water?
A bottle!
It's a miracle!
Throw!
If I throw this in...
Maybe I'll learn how to craft a money trough.
Should I do it?
Oh my god, let's try it!
Oh, I can't. Wait. Is it because I...
Hup!
Rip. Hold on. I actually kind of need that.
Oh no!
Oi!
Alright, it was worth a try.
Interesting how you can throw it away like that.
Are the items still in?
They are!
That was a bit risky of me, actually.
What if I lost all my items?
That was a bit questionable.
I will admit that.
Whoops. Nice.
Okay, back we go.
Alright, man. Dude, I definitely want to make a home here.
This is freaking awesome.
I'll be careful now.
I'm focusing so hard.
Oh no!
Oh, I think I'm gonna get caught.
Ah, shit!
Dammit!
Oh, where am I?
Crap!
This mysterious liquid is fucking with me.
But you know what?
I like it.
Me likey.
Me likey liquidy.
Get up here.
Back to work.
Uh, remove this.
Oh, we're gonna get caught here for sure.
Hold on.
Open the floodgates!
Up!
Oh no, no, no, no!
Not that way! Not that way!
Not that way!
Block it!
Ah!
Oh no!
Don't fall in!
Ah, this is a mess.
This is a mess.
I wonder what happens if I throw a bomb in there.
Dude, I wish I had a bomb on me right now.
Yo, what about a monster lasagna?
A vertebra.
Thank you.
An acorn.
Just one acorn.
It shall become a magical tree.
No.
This can be deleted, actually.
Um...
I'm tempted to throw a weapon in.
I can always craft it again, I guess, but...
No.
These weapons are too valuable for me.
Either...
torch.
How did I just get that?
Alright, um...
Don't fall in!
Oh, that was close.
Make my way up here.
There we go.
So what I want to do now is...
Flow away!
Nice!
Look at this, I'm making a nice... pool.
Yeah.
What just happened?
Something became dirt just now.
And I'm not sure what it was.
I wonder if I can have, like, an armor set.
That will make me immune to the effects of this water.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Equalize.
Come on. A bit more.
Don't!
No one died.
I'm gonna use the stone now.
Why can't I?
I'm finally learning the hammer, man.
I feel like that took way too long for me.
There we go!
Look at that.
And then I'm gonna have a house...
above it.
How about that?
Dude!
How about a house hanging from the ceiling?
Huh?
So it's like...
stilts...
but inversed.
Stilts...
to the power of minus one.
I feel like that's very...
something...
of this location here that is very mysterious.
You know?
Also...
What the hell?
I made some very weird digs here.
I gotta be honest, this is some weird shit I made here.
Hello? There we go.
This shouldn't affect me?
Nope. Good.
Flow downstream.
There you go.
What have we got?
Doesn't matter, it's gone now.
Failings.
Ah, I don't have my thing on me.
Dammit.
Kill it.
Okay, it doesn't do anything.
I need to make a bit of room here.
This is like the ultimate...
construction stream here.
This is so risky.
I should just make a platform below me, actually.
Why am I making this so difficult on myself?
I'll do that in a second.
Ah!
I'm okay.
Temporary platform engage.
Where is it?
Huh? Where'd he go?
Ah, there it is. I threw it away.
There we go.
What's that?
Oh, it's just stone.
I'm gonna make a bit more room here.
It's not gonna look like much in the beginning, but I promise this is gonna turn out to be incredible.
This project right here is ambitious, it's bold, it's nasty.
The three most important things to me in life.
Okay, I think this is about almost good enough.
Let's make a little bit more here.
Nope, that's too much.
And disable that and just go manual now.
There we go.
Now the question now is...
How do I efficiently do this quick?
There is no way to do this quick.
Actually, it doesn't matter.
As long as I fill up this part here.
There we go.
And then we have a way down as well.
I just want one of those tunnels to be...
Actually, maybe I'll remove this side.
Because then I can fall down from the other side when I'm up top.
Yep, that seems better.
And now...
Let's see.
How should the house be hanging is the question.
Do I have a workbench?
I can make one.
Plan.
And then...
It should be made of...
Let's think here.
Let's have it made of...
Oh, dude, I have an even more crazy idea for a house style.
Holy shit!
I have an idea!
It's gonna be a little hard to execute, I think.
Hmm...
How am I gonna do this?
It's... okay.
Hold on.
Let's...
Oh, this is gonna be nuts.
This is gonna be completely illegal.
Completely illegal.
And now I need to make...
Slowly go a little further down here.
Okay, this is a good start.
Let's see if I can do this.
This is gonna be so finicky.
Because it's so difficult, I can't go in the liquid.
I can stand here though, right?
Ah, nice.
Okay...
How am I gonna do this, man?
How am I gonna do this?
Let's see, what if I do this?
That?
Dammit, it's still there!
Huh.
Let me think about this.
Actually, I have a better solution to this.
I have a better solution.
I think I know what to do now.
Yo!
Don't fall in.
I need to go down here now.
Oh.
It became dirt.
My plan is the following, I'll show you.
Go up here.
This is a good start.
Oh yeah, it's looking good, boys!
Oh yeah!
Oh, this is gonna be so nice.
I guess I could use explosions.
You just don't have any bombs on me right now.
And the way home is way too long.
Here's the way I'm going home, dude.
No way!
I'm too close to this magnificent end result that I'm approaching here.
And when I get there, you're not gonna believe what you're seeing.
It's gonna blow your mind.
The ingenuity and the boldness of this plan is unparalleled, I think, in the world of Terraria.
Nobody has ever seen the likes of what I'm about to do here.
It's gonna be crazy.
Actually, crazy is not even gonna cut it.
We need a whole new adjective to describe what I'm about to do.
That's right.
Okay, let's be careful here now.
Let me get the lead out of there.
Oh yeah, baby.
In fact, let me use this one a bit more.
Auto-mine.
Auto-mining.
Yeah, that's good.
Make sure that's automatic.
This is... this is kind of odd.
Oh!
Nice!
Good start!
Let's be careful now.
Oh yeah!
Yeah, baby!
Oh, hello!
Oh, I can't... that's getting a little dangerous now.
Let's be careful.
Drain this water.
Nice!
And then...
Okay, now we gotta be extra careful.
Let's see here.
Extra careful.
Go up here.
Move all of that crap.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is gonna be so sick.
Dude, I'm buzzing with excitement.
Damn it!
That was not what I intended to do.
But it's okay.
I gotta be careful here.
Why isn't that working?
Why can't I...
Do we have a bullshit here?
Aha! We did have a bullshit!
I knew it!
Right?
Dude, I'm so focused.
I'm hyper-focused.
Okay, now let me take these Ethereum blocks.
They actually look kinda cool.
And I do want them in my life.
Go that way.
Okay, now...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What did I just get?
Strange brew, I think.
Weird, how that just dispatched some of that.
Oh, I guess I covered it up with stone.
So there was technically still liquid behind it.
That's how that works.
Which is interesting.
So hold on, how am I gonna do this?
Precisely.
It's tricky, it's very tricky.
This is actually insanely tricky.
I need to sort of...
Oh my god, hold on.
So it falls, right?
We need small holes.
Oh yeah, we need holes!
That's the solution!
We're gonna go like this.
There.
Interesting how I don't fall through the holes, by the way, when they're not large enough.
I can't drop through here.
Oh yeah, this is the answer to all my issues.
We're needing holes.
Let's make some lights as well.
Like that.
Got down here for a moment.
I wonder if I can pick up the shimmer liquid there with my bucket.
Deposit all, please.
Get it out of there.
Oh, I'm sliding around on this!
It's slippery!
That's fun.
Okay, this looks...
Now I have to decide.
This is not pushing me through, it seems.
Let me actually do this.
I need to get rid of this anyway.
Nice!
We wanna fill up this entire place.
I love this music in the background.
I feel like it's perfect.
For the madness that's happening right now.
Okay, that looks good to me.
That looks like a good amount.
Let's rotate that.
Like that.
Ah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stupid auto thingy.
Now we go this way.
Oh, and we can even use the stuff on the left to help.
Oh, yeah, baby.
This is lovely.
I do need to get rid of this.
Some of this.
It's gonna drain.
But actually, I do wanna...
Everything's gonna come together here.
Okay, let's be careful now.
I'm having fun, man.
This is great.
I love this.
This is absolutely fantastic.
Will you stop?
Okay, rid of that.
Let's think here.
Okay.
Yep.
So that goes like that.
And I go, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's gonna do the thing.
I need to remove more.
The important part is, though, that I be conservative now.
I need to do something like this.
First.
Just for...
It's one of those situations and, like...
You know when there's food on the table, you...
Instead of taking a big portion first.
You don't do that.
You take a small portion because you can always take more after.
Right?
In case you can't eat it all.
Same thing here.
Same principle.
Maybe I cannot eat all this at once.
That lunch is too big for my tummy.
And sadness will ensue.
What is that place, by the way?
Look at the background there.
Doesn't that look interesting?
Okay, okay.
Nice.
I like it so far.
Now I need to be strategic about this.
Let's see here.
Don't fuck up now.
This is a big deal.
Let me remove the outer ones first.
They're all going to get turned into dirt, huh?
I guess that's what stone is. It's just dirt.
Or dirt is just stone.
It's just a lot of small stones.
So shouldn't it be the other way around?
Actually, I guess both ways work.
Oh, what's happening?
Something spawned right on top of me just now.
Okay.
Now I can remove all this as well.
Angry shackle!
And a diamond!
Cool.
I need to be so careful here.
There we go.
Okay.
Nice.
So far, so good.
Now...
Oh, no, no. Don't fall in. Don't fall in.
Please die.
Thank you.
Why can't I...
I can't hold on to this look.
The liquid is almost dripping through a thing.
Isn't that interesting?
Really?
There it is, look.
Yeah, it's hiding behind the block.
But it's not hiding behind these. Isn't that interesting? Why is that?
Shit, how do I...
I gotta be careful here.
Why is it so much fun, dude?
Like, I gotta say, like, building? Also in Minecraft, it's actually something that surprised me a little bit about myself.
I guess I like doing this stuff.
I thought maybe I didn't like that sort of stuff, but I do.
Okay, I have to be up here real quick first.
I'm doing this so carefully, man, because I know if I don't, it's not gonna work the way I think it is.
Shit, I can't reach.
Still can't reach.
I gotta make a little hole here.
Plop! Lock that.
Back we go.
Down here.
Now we're gonna drain.
And there you go.
Yes, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain.
Also that one, please.
All of it, thank you.
Perfect amount as well.
Very nice.
Oops, oh, there was something hiding there. Interesting.
It just goes down there now, okay.
Okay.
There's also some hiding in there.
Nice.
It's sort of flowing over here now, but that's okay.
That is actually A-okay, as they say.
All right, guys.
My plan is almost there.
Maybe you have guessed what it is by now.
I think it's kind of obvious at this point.
There's really no hiding it anymore.
I was trying to be coy about it all.
Oh, I have so many platforms.
I'm actually gonna use some.
I need to be a little lower, I think.
Like that.
There we go.
Bop, bop.
Let me think here.
Like this.
Okay, that's good.
Maybe one more here.
Okay, not bad.
And then...
I'm working in the dark here a lot.
Let's put a torch.
All right, look at the background. There's also gems and shit right there.
That is intriguing.
Now I wanna do...
Let's see, let me think.
I guess...
The problem is, if my math is off here, and when I say math, I didn't really do any.
I'm just fucking crossing my fingers and hoping.
This should be...
the place of my dreams.
Oh, but wait!
Hold on, I almost fucked up!
We need a...
Okay, okay, actually.
We can do that after.
Yeah, yeah, no worries.
Everything's fine.
The plan is intact.
Do that.
It's... yeah.
Actually, we don't even need these holes here anymore.
I don't think so at least.
Okay, let me think.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let me go over here.
Move that one.
Get to this side now.
There.
And...
Let's see here.
I actually need to do a little bit of repelling here.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Step here.
Like that.
And then...
I kinda need to be down there somehow, but I can't really.
Actually, I can!
Hold on!
I'm an idiot!
Of course I can!
I just do a...
This is a...
Like that.
I'm not gonna fall through yet.
Even here.
I can remove this safely.
Good.
Now.
Wait, now there's water inside of this.
Or the thingy.
I need to...
I need to get below there.
How do I do that without fucking this up?
Ah, no.
It's too late for me.
Okay.
Like here.
Let me safety make a little bit more of a thing here.
It's almost time!
I'm so excited to see how this...
This is gonna probably either be amazing or it's gonna fail spectacularly.
Those are the two only options I see.
There's just no other...
There's no middle way.
Middle ground here.
It's...
That's how it is.
Okay.
I need to be smart about this.
What's happening?
Looks like Bradley Dante and Lion Pines are throwing a party?!
Wait, really?
They're throwing a party because everyone moved away!
I almost gotta go back now to check that out, but hold on.
I think this is what I want.
Alright.
Let's try it.
Here we go!
All or nothing!
Actually, uh...
Let me start on this side.
I need to do this very precisely here.
Let's see.
Can I reach? I can reach.
It needs to be from the bottom.
Okay.
Go!
Oh no!
No!
No, no, no!
Don't put me here!
Not yet!
No!
Get me back!
How am I gonna get up?
How am I gonna get back up there?
Oh no!
It's gonna FLOT!
No!
Emergency flooding shelter!
Emergency!
No!
Let's totally know how that works in real life, but...
Yes!
Okay, okay.
Let's get back there.
Holy shit!
Come on!
Sully the Cool Slime?
Fuck off!
I like Cool Slimes.
Cool Slimes are my favorite.
Oh man!
Okay, I'm kinda scared here.
This is, uh...
This is very trap-y looking.
Whoop!
Let's get back up here.
Okay, we're fine.
We're definitely fine here.
This is all good.
It's going according to plan.
Oh, I thought you were the Cool Slime.
Oh no!
Don't fall, don't fall!
Don't fall!
Fuck!
This is such a mess!
Kill it!
There we go.
Alright, alright, alright.
We're fine.
We're absolutely...
Oh, but wait a minute.
Yeah, yeah, we're absolutely fine.
Oh yeah.
Plan is intact.
Yeah!
And now...
What do you think of that?
Oh wait, we're not done.
We are not done.
Oh wait, how am I gonna get this over there?
How am I gonna do that?
I have an idea.
Let's see here.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't fall off.
Walk off.
Um...
How do I push up?
I wanna push it up.
I need to push it up.
Push, push, push, push.
Hmm, how do I push it up?
Let me do a quick experiment here.
Let's say I go down here.
Oh wait, there's liquid in these.
Hey, that's not bad, actually.
Yeah, yeah, take it out of there.
More the better.
Hell yeah.
That's what I like to see.
There we go.
Fill it up.
And there's no more here.
Okay.
If I were to go...
Oh, let's be careful here.
Let's say I do that.
Like that.
And then I dig down.
Can I push liquid up like this?
Not really.
Doesn't work like that, unfortunately.
So the liquid is like in a state behind the blocks, it seems.
So yeah, that's...
That's weird.
I do, you know what?
I gotta go back anyway because I need to check whether or not I can use a bucket to transport this stuff.
And I want to check out the party they're having.
Ludo has a party hat on.
Try Swirly Pink and Purple, it works, I swear.
What's with the party?
Did you make sure your device was plugged in?
You know, that's a good question.
Or suggestion.
Engineering helmet.
Ransomproofed wire vision.
I gotta experiment with the wire stuff at some point.
Very intriguing.
Everyone's wearing party hats.
So who was throwing the party?
Bradley, Dante and Lion Pines.
Bradley, Dante.
Wait a minute, Dante isn't even here.
He shouldn't be at least.
Wait, where's Dante?
Dante's here!
No, wait, yeah, yeah, he's there, he's there.
Huh?
So when he throws a party, everyone parties.
Everyone parties.
Alright, well...
Never been to a party before!
You might want to check around with the others.
People sometimes bring out special party favors.
Really?
Well...
Okay, there's no party favors there.
Maybe Seymour.
What a blustery day, stay a while and buy a thing or two.
Forest pylon!
Yoink!
Why is that here now?
I guess the party did the trick.
Party?
Let's put that...
Somewhere out here, I guess, for now.
Right there.
Beautiful!
We now have a teleportation system.
Fucking fantastic.
Party favors mortal?
You don't sell anything? Do you say anything else?
Just like the number of people? Yeah, I'm gonna move you, don't worry about it.
You don't have anything new?
Well, in that case, let me use my new pylon...
to go...
I guess I wanna...
Let me go... Oh wait, I don't have one over there.
I was gonna talk to the party girl.
But don't say through the party.
Don't spray and pay and pray in the wind, buddy.
Nothing new. Are you gonna say anything else?
Okay.
I truly love parties. So many beautiful colors and happy people.
I wonder if prizes are reduced during parties. Is that like the benefit? Is that the party favor?
That they speak of.
Okay, I'm gonna go back here anyway.
Oh wait, I came back here because I needed something. The bucket!
Let me quickly go grab the bucket.
Bucket first.
Should be in Michelinius.
Oh my god, I'm such a god.
You see me remember that just now that quickly? Yeah.
Steel trap. That's right.
Let me try something.
Actually amazing. Totally works.
I wonder if this works on the Shiver liquid.
We're gonna try it.
We're definitely trying that.
What if I gain speed by walking here? And then I transport into this.
No, I lose the momentum. Okay.
That's too bad.
What if I do this to accelerate?
That's a bit difficult to do.
Okay, let's see if I can grab that.
Let me actually experiment with water at first a little bit.
Okay, yeah, it's definitely transporting liquid like that.
So now that I go down here,
I got the... Did I take some out? Hold on.
Let me take a look at the water level.
I think I did. A very tiny amount. Look. Yeah, that's awesome.
It's gotta work. It's gotta work.
Please tell me this works. I really need this to work.
Okay, come on.
Holy shit, I've also been going for quite a while now.
I'm gonna test this real quick and then I have to stop.
I really do.
I got so into this, I kind of forgot that I was hungry.
It's like I just remembered. Oh, yeah, right. I'm starving.
Fucking games, man.
What they do to you.
All this water here is annoying.
Come on.
I'm so slow.
Come on, momentum. Speed.
That's what I'm talking about. Now we're fast.
Wait, I have to go down here. Actually, first, talk to Party Girl.
I want to see if anyone's gonna have anything, it's her.
Party up. You're like in charge of the cake, Oliver.
Am I?
Oh, he's here now. Fjell. Finally.
Smoke. Wait, where's the cake?
Wait, what cake?
Fireworks box.
Okay.
Fjell?
Oh, I got... oh!
Stuff your face. Stuff someone else's face. Whatever.
I can't stuff my own face.
Hey, Fjell.
Oh, I can place it. Oh!
I went to Sweden once. They party hard. Why aren't you like that?
You're about to be evicted if you keep talking like that.
I will evict you. Okay?
A picronata.
Oh my god.
Oh, Izzy.
No, don't quest me.
No, I didn't want to.
We go down.
Into the hole.
Go, go, gadget, bucket.
What is this tree anyway?
It's a stone tree.
Wow.
Will you... die?
Okay.
The moment of truth.
Oh, no.
Come on, please.
No, it doesn't work.
No.
No, man.
Wait, how am I going to do this then?
My plan.
Huh?
Hmm.
If only real physics applied here, huh?
Party time's over.
You're right, it is.
You're right.
Guys, I don't have time to chat. I gotta get out of here.
I need to eat. I need to do things.
I need to pee. I need to...
slew.
You know?
I am lost for words.
I will quickly say...
Hold on, let me open chat real quick.
Thank you for watching, guys.
This was amazing.
This was a nice, relaxing stream.
I actually forgot that I was tired.
Can you believe it? It's either the game or the coffee that I drank.
I drank quite a lot. I have a huge cup of it.
It just slew.
Damn right, man. I love slewing.
I love slewing and I love sleuthing.
First ever note death stream! Oh my god!
That's what I'm talking about!
I guess I cheated a little bit by not trying to do dangerous things.
But I finally did it.
Hell yeah. I mean, I did do a bunch of combat.
There was a King Slime, right?
Yeah?
That's right. That was a boss.
Okay, guys, this was fucking awesome.
Thank you for watching and enjoying.
Like and subscribe, all that.
Join the Discord if you haven't yet.
The community there is slapping.
So yeah, I'll see you guys in the next stream or video.
Have a good one! Adios.